good morning thank you for your patience
早上好，谢谢您的耐心配合
thanks for coming to this talk today as
感谢您今天参加本次演讲
well so I'm going to talk today about
好，所以我今天要谈
collection and reduction in the stream
流中的收集和减少
in the stream API this is a talk about
在流API中，这是关于
basically about Java 8 so the idea of it
基本上是关于Java 8的
is if you've been using the stream API
如果您一直在使用流API
or if you haven't been using the stream
或者如果您尚未使用流
API but you aren't
API，但您不是
but either way you aren't really very
但是无论哪种方式你都不是很
confident about the quite large subset
对相当大的子集充满信心
of that API which has to do with
与该API有关的
collectors then this talk is meant to be
收藏家，那么这个谈话本来是
for you so I'm not going to spend a lot
给你，所以我不会花很多钱
of time on streams as a whole I'm not
从整体上看，我不是
going to I'm going to assume mostly that
我将主要假设
we know we know roughly what's going on
我们知道我们大致了解发生了什么
there and we're going to focus
在那里，我们将集中精力
particularly on this one particular
特别是在这一点上
operation it turns out that it's quite a
操作证明，这是一个相当
large API and it's actually worth
大型API，它实际上值得
delving into because you can do a lot
钻研，因为你可以做很多事情
with it and I hoped to show that during
用它，我希望表明
this during this talk so so just just
在这次谈话中，所以只是
who I am if you've heard of me then it's
如果你听说过我，那我就是谁
because I've written these books on a
因为我已经将这些书写在
couple of books on Java and if you
几本关于Java的书，如果您
haven't and that's not entirely
还没有，那还不完全是
surprising I like to say the Java 5 book
令人惊讶的是我喜欢说Java 5书
is the best book in print the best book
是印刷中最好的书
at all are devoted to generics I'm
完全致力于我的仿制药
concerned that without any fear of
担心而不必担心
contradiction that joke has lasted 10
笑话持续了10年的矛盾
years it's obviously the only one I
年显然是我唯一的
couldn't say it couldn't be so certain
不能说不能那么确定
otherwise and then I wrote a book on
否则我就写了一本书
Java and the but in this book which is
Java和本书中的
really about streams although it's got
真的关于流，尽管它有
lambdas in the title it's really much
标题中的lambdas确实很多
more about streams in about lambdas is
关于lambdas中的流的更多信息是
what this talk is based on so and and
这次谈话的依据是
then I'm a champion and I'm the Java one
那我是冠军，我是Java
rock star and stuff like that um so the
摇滚明星和诸如此类的东西，所以
agenda for today is I'm going to talk
今天的议程是我要谈的
about why we want collectors and what
关于我们为什么要收藏家以及什么
that's about that actually takes up
那就是实际上占用了
quite a lot of the top because I think
相当多的顶部，因为我认为
because I think having some background
因为我认为有一些背景
on what's going on is quite useful then
在发生的事情上很有用
I'm going to talk about the predefined
我将谈论预定义的
collectors that are provided by the by
由...提供的收集器
the the framework and then we'll
框架，然后我们将
probably take a break if I haven't used
如果我不习惯的话，可能会休息一下
up all of my time with fiddling around
摆弄我所有的时间
with cables and we'll take a five-minute
用电缆，我们需要五分钟
break and then we'll do some worked
休息，然后我们将做一些工作
examples and and the idea that this is
例子和想法，这是
that you're going to you're going to
你将要去
write the code for me if I can manage to
如果可以的话，请为我编写代码
get IntelliJ up without touching the
不用触摸即可启动IntelliJ
cable then well
电缆那么好
a bit of live coding in the second half
下半年进行一些现场编码
and actually see some use of these
并实际看到这些的一些用途
collectors and then finally there's a
收藏家，然后终于有一个
there's a very short section maybe 10 or
有一个很短的部分，也许10或
15 minutes just to round off the talk
15分钟只是为了结束谈话
about how you how and why you would
关于你如何以及为什么会
write your own collector so the example
写你自己的收藏家，所以这个例子
domain for the talk is made as simple as
讨论的领域变得如此简单
possible we just have a value object a
可能我们只有一个价值对象
person with three fields a city which I
我的三个城市的人
presume to be an enum but we never
假定是一个枚举，但我们从未
actually never actually see it defined
实际上从来没有真正看到它的定义
and and a string field and and an int
和一个字符串字段和一个int
field so the idea that is to have a
领域，所以有一个想法
couple of reference fields and and the
几个参考字段和
primitive field cause that because that
原始字段是因为
works differently and that gives us some
工作方式不同，这给了我们一些
different problems and the kind of code
不同的问题和代码种类
that we'll be seeing is really as simple
我们将看到的真的很简单
as it could reasonably be we're going to
因为这可能是合理的，我们要
be creating a new person and we're going
建立一个新的人，我们要
to we're going to be making a list of
我们将要列出
person objects and then we're going to
人对象，然后我们将
be seeing the different things that can
看到可以
happen if you use that as a source of a
如果您将其用作来源
stream and essentially what we're going
流，本质上是我们要去的
to be doing is operations on that and on
要做的就是在那上面进行操作
the streams that are produced that way
以这种方式产生的溪流
and then we'll then we're going to
然后我们将要
collect them and we'll see what the
收集它们，我们将看到
collective is about so just to take it
集体就是要接受它
for a little while just to take a kind
一会儿只是为了一种
of higher level view what's going on
更高级别的视图发生了什么
what's going on in the stream well the
流中发生了什么
life of a stream element is is it begins
流元素的生命是开始吗
at a at a splitter rate that's how it's
以这样的速度分配
born so the idea of a splitter ater is
出生，所以分离器的想法是
it's it's a kind of cute name for
这是一个可爱的名字
something that can both iterate and
既可以迭代又可以
split and so it iterates if it's
分裂，因此，如果它是迭代
processing the stream sequentially
按顺序处理流
because it feeds the elements of the
因为它养活了
stream in feeds the elements from its
流中的饲料元素
source into the stream one by one so
源流一个接一个地流
that's iteration as we know it and and
这就是我们所知道的迭代，并且
it can also do under certain
在某些情况下也可以
circumstances it will it will also split
在这种情况下它也会分裂
the the its source imagine say an array
它的来源想象说一个数组
or a ray list then you can see that the
或射线列表，那么您可以看到
that you could process that more
你可以处理更多
efficiently if you had parallel hardware
如果您有并行硬件，则效率很高
by first breaking it down into into into
首先将其分解为
sections each of them being suitable for
每个部分都适合
until you have as many sections
直到你有尽可能多的部分
essentially as you have cause to execute
基本上是因为您有执行的理由
on so in this case I'm imagining that
在这种情况下，我在想
we've got a
我们有一个
an ArrayList or an array and it's split
ArrayList或数组并将其拆分
in two it's been split twice into 4 into
一分为二
4 pieces because it's executing on 4
4件，因为它在4件上执行
core hardware all this is done
核心硬件这一切都完成了
automatically for you by the by the by
由by自动为您
the stream API if you want it to happen
如果您希望流API发生
all you need to do if you want to if you
如果需要，您需要做的所有事情
want to get the difference between a
想要得到一个之间的区别
sequential stream with in which case the
顺序流，在这种情况下
splitter ATAR is just iterating you just
分离器ATAR只是在迭代您而已
say I want to stream and if you want to
说我想直播，如果你想
and if you want a parallel stream as
如果你想并行流作为
we're going to see here because each one
我们将在这里看到，因为每个
of these yellow things is a pipeline and
这些黄色的东西是一条管道，
in and essentially the different threads
在本质上是不同的线程
attached to each of the different cause
依附于每个不同的原因
it's executing the the code for the for
它正在执行for的代码
the stream pipeline on each one of the
每个流媒体流上的流水线
data sets each one of those subsets and
数据集每个子集和
and if you want that to happen you'd say
如果你想做到这一点，你会说
I want a parallel stream instead of
我想要并行流而不是
saying I want to stream and it's really
说我想直播，这真的
as easy as that whether you'll actually
就这么简单，无论您是否真的
make any real gains from doing that it's
通过这样做可以真正获得收益
a different matter
另一件事
because for to get a significant
因为为了获得重大
improvement in performance by going
通过不断改进性能
parallel as we say requires that
正如我们所说，并行要求
requires a number of conditions that may
需要一些条件，可能
not that aren't met in many common cases
并非在许多常见情况下都无法满足
but it's so the idea of the building
但这就是建筑的想法
parallelism in was was that it should be
并行性是应该
explicit but unobtrusive that was a
明确但不引人注目的是
slogan of the stream of the stream
流的口号
designers and and they and they
设计师以及他们与他们
succeeded it is it is parallel it is
成功的是它是并行的
explicit it is unobtrusive it's very
明确的是，它并不引人注目
easy to use and probably too easy to use
易于使用，可能太容易使用了
because many people have been quite
因为很多人
disappointed not being not having fully
感到失望的是没有充分
understood the situation in which you'll
了解您会遇到的情况
get benefits they sometimes have been
获得他们有时曾经获得的利益
disappointed so what happens is then the
失望，那么接下来会发生什么
elements come down these the elements
元素归结为这些元素
come down these different pipelines and
通过这些不同的渠道
then they're collected by it by a
然后他们被一个
terminal operation so these so the three
终端操作，所以这三个
that so the three stages of the life
所以生命的三个阶段
style lifetime of a stream element are
流元素的样式生存期是
the the splitter ATAR where where
分离器ATAR在哪里
they're born the intermediate operations
他们出生于中间阶段
where they're transformed and they're
他们在哪里转变，他们在
finally collected by a terminal
最终由码头收集
operation and we're going to and we're
操作，我们要去，我们要
going to be concentrating on the
将专注于
collector I should say probably that
收藏家我应该说
although I've kind of although in that
虽然我有点
little introduction I've not been very
一点介绍，我不是很
positive about parallel execution the
对并行执行持肯定态度
idea of parallel execution was still
并行执行的想法仍然存在
very
非常
to the stream API designers because what
给流API设计者，因为
they wanted was to make sure that the
他们想要确保
code that you wrote the code that you
您编写的代码您编写的代码
write for streams should be equally
写流应该相等
executable either in parallel or
可并行执行或
sequentially you may get very different
依次地，您可能会变得非常不同
performance depending on depending on
性能取决于
your particular hardware setup and other
您特定的硬件设置和其他
things but the but functionally it
东西，但在功能上
should work in exactly the same way so
应该以完全相同的方式工作
this is a very important design
这是非常重要的设计
motivation and sometimes you think there
动力，有时你认为
are things missing from the stream API
流API缺少什么
why why can't I do this
为什么我为什么不能这样做
and the answer is because you couldn't
答案是因为你不能
do it in parallel and if you can't do it
并行执行，如果无法执行
in parallel then you can't do it you
并行，那么你做不到
can't do it at all in the stream API so
根本无法在流API中做到这一点，因此
I call in the book that in the book on
我称这本书为
lambdas I call this parallel ready code
我称之为并行准备代码
so you even if your code isn't going to
所以即使你的代码不会
be executed in parallel it should be
可以并行执行
ready to be executed in parallel and
准备并行执行
they see that as the way forward for for
他们认为这是前进的道路
collections processing in Java okay so
用Java处理集合好吗
the so now I'm going to focus on the
所以现在我将专注于
terminal operations a bit there's three
终端操作有点三
kinds of these and I'm only going to go
这些种类，我只会去
through two of them very briefly because
通过他们中的两个非常简短，因为
I'm not interested in I'm really
我对我真的不感兴趣
interested in the third one very much
对第三个非常感兴趣
the search operations are things that
搜索操作就是
all match and any match and find any and
全部匹配和任何匹配并找到任何和
find first C's these these terminal
找到第一个C这些这些终端
operations are the things that actually
操作实际上是
pull the data down the stream down down
下拉数据流
the stream in it so you could set a
它中的流，因此您可以设置一个
stream up by saying I want I want I want
说我要我要我要
a stream but until you actually say
一条小溪，但是直到你真正说出
until you actually provide a terminal
直到您实际提供一个终端
operation start the execution of that
操作开始执行
nothing moves so here what we're saying
没有任何动静，所以我们在说什么
is we want to we want to get back a
是我们想要我们想要回来
boolean corresponding to whether or not
布尔值对应于是否
all of all of the adults all sorry all
所有的成年人都对不起
of the person objects in that in the in
人的对象在
that people list have have an age field
人员列表中有年龄字段
of greater than 21 and if they do then
大于21，如果他们这样做
that'll be true and if not that'll be
那将是真的，如果不是，那将会是
false find any and fine first working
虚假发现任何问题，并且可以优先工作
something like the same way they
就像他们一样
returned an optional because they're
返回一个可选的，因为它们是
looking for something that meets a
寻找符合
condition and it might not be there and
条件，它可能不存在，
it might be there these things that
可能有这些东西
these these are called short-circuit
这些叫做短路
operations and they're quite important
操作，它们非常重要
from the point of view of processing
从加工的角度
infinite streams because of all of these
由于所有这些，无限的流
search operations will stop when they've
搜索操作将停止
when they're when they're satisfied so
当他们感到满意时
for example in the case of the example
例如在例子中
the example code there
那里的示例代码
if the
如果
could you could have you could have a
你能拥有一个吗
really long list of people person
真的很长的人名单
objects and you could be processing them
对象，您可能正在处理它们
sequentially and if the first one is not
按顺序，如果第一个不是
an adult the first one has an age of
第一个成年人的年龄为
lesson two of less than 21 then
少于21的第二课
processing will stop so it doesn't need
处理将停止，因此不需要
to process the whole stream in order to
处理整个流以便
in order to evaluate the condition so
为了评估病情
these short circuit operations are very
这些短路操作非常
useful without them you actually
没有他们，你实际上很有用
couldn't do anything useful with
无法做任何有用的事情
infinite streams the second kind of
无限流第二种
terminal operation our side affecting
终端操作我们这边影响
operations everyone loves these because
每个人都喜欢这些操作，因为
they look like you know what you're used
他们看起来像你知道你用了什么
to
至
so if you see you've got but so you've
所以如果你看到你有，但是你有
got for each and every one says alright
每个人都有说的好
okay I really can do it eration here so
好吧，我真的可以在这里做到
one of the points I'm going to be making
我要提出的观点之一
in this talk is you really can't do it
在这个谈话中，你真的做不到
eration any longer you see for each you
每个人看到的同盟
think hey I can do it eration so so for
认为我可以做到，所以对于
example for reached here takes a
这里到达的示例需要一个
consumer that's something that just
消费者就是
takes the value and doesn't and and does
取值，不取而代之
something with it but doesn't return
有东西但不返回
anything and we've got here that we're
任何东西，我们来到这里，我们
going to print out each of the person
要打印出每个人
objects each of the personal objects in
反对每个个人对象
the stream so the first question is
流，所以第一个问题是
could we maybe use these use these
我们可以使用这些吗
terminal operations these side affecting
终端操作这些方面的影响
operations
运作
they're called side affecting operations
它们被称为侧面影响操作
because they do something to over to a
因为他们做了一些事情以结束
value that's outside of the stream could
流之外的价值可以
we maybe do that by calculating it's the
我们也许可以通过计算得出
total of the ages of the of the person
该人的总年龄
objects in that list will that work
该列表中的对象将起作用
sequential or parallel will it work
顺序或并行工作
well okay listen that's that's that's
好吧，那是那样的
interesting so the answer was sequential
有趣，所以答案是连续的
II it will work in parallel it won't
II它将并行运行，不会
work naturally that's slightly off
自然工作，这有点不对劲
actually this won't compile the beacon
实际上这不会编译信标
because because some is some is not
因为因为有些是一些不是
final that's the kind of that's that's a
最后就是那种
sort of trivial answer because then
琐碎的答案，因为
you'll say you'll fold your arms and
你会说你会交叉双臂
you'll say ha why did they put this
你会说哈他们为什么把这个
stupid restriction on some has to be
对某些事物的愚蠢限制
final or actually as we now say
最后或实际上我们现在说的
effectively final so why did that why
有效地决赛，那为什么呢？
did they do that well the reason why
他们做得很好吗
they did that was because of what I said
他们这样做是因为我说的
a moment ago which is that it should
刚才是应该的
work properly in parallel and you're
并行正常工作，您
kind of right that it won't work in
一种权利，它不会起作用
parallel it won't work in parallel
并行将无法并行工作
because not because I mean supposing we
因为不是因为我的意思是假设我们
we did some trick to get around the
我们做了一些技巧来绕过
effectively final thing we could make
实际上，我们可以做的最后一件事
some into a field or we could use the 1
一些进入一个领域，或者我们可以使用1
element array trick or something like
元素数组技巧或类似的东西
that but even if you could write this
那，即使你可以写这个
you wouldn't want to
你不想
and the reason you wouldn't want to is
而你不想的原因是
because some if you imagine it executing
因为有些，如果你想象它正在执行
in parallel this variable sum will be
并行地，该变量和为
hot it's gonna have to be accessed by
很热，必须由
every single thread right so every
每个线程都正确，所以每个
single thread will have to will have to
单线程将不得不
get hold of it and and the reason why
掌握它以及原因
you're saying it won't work I guess is
你是说这行不通，我猜是
because it's not guarded here you would
因为这里没有有人看守
have to synchronize on it and that would
必须同步它，这将
be a tremendous overhead that would just
将会是巨大的开销
be really that would completely remove
真的会完全删除
the point of having parallel processing
进行并行处理的要点
in the first place if you had if you
首先，如果有的话
have to synchronize on every access to
必须在每次访问时进行同步
some so we really should not calculate
一些，所以我们真的不应该计算
ages anything like this it's not just
像这样的年龄不只是
not just this particular example but
不只是这个例子
anything which which uses an accumulator
任何使用蓄电池的东西
effectively we're going to have to get
有效地，我们将必须获得
we're going to have to stop doing that
我们将不得不停止这样做
and the and the argument of the stream
和流的和参数
designer this was that not only we
设计师，这不仅是我们
shouldn't feel we shouldn't feel bad
不应该感到我们不应该感到难过
about this we should be pleased because
关于这一点，我们应该感到高兴，因为
we're going to find a better way of
我们将找到一种更好的方法
coding so they have a quite an
编码，所以他们有一个相当
evangelistic attitude in the in the
传福音的态度
design of the stream API there's a push
流API的设计有一个推动
towards functional programming and and
进行函数式编程和
you'll see I hope that it actually gets
你会看到我希望它真的能
results so so
结果如此
so we're gonna use reduction this test
所以我们要使用减少测试
now I get on to the kind of terminal
现在我进入那种终端
operation I'm really interested in which
操作我真的很感兴趣
is reduction so what's the difference
是减少，所以有什么区别
between between reduction and and used
在减少和使用之间
and why do we want it I suppose is it is
为什么我们想要它，我想是
the question here so here I've got the
这里的问题，所以我在这里
the kind of code that you would imagine
您会想到的那种代码
writing if you wanted to calculate the
如果您想计算
total of the values in an array and here
数组中所有值的总和
I've got here I've got an execution
我到这里了我被处死了
graph of it just very very roughly you
它的图形只是非常非常粗略的你
can see that what's going to happen is
可以看到将要发生的是
that the way that this the execution of
这种执行的方式
that statement in blue there is going to
那条蓝色的语句将
involve repeated additions to the same
涉及重复添加相同的
variable so first of all we get the
变量，所以首先我们得到
value 0 we add 1 to it then we got it
值0我们将其加1然后得到
value 2 now that we have that to the to
值2现在我们已经到
the value we've accumulated and so on
我们积累的价值，依此类推
and that and that of course is going to
那，那当然是要
be is going to give this this huge
将会给这个巨大的
problem that I mentioned that that we're
我提到我们的问题
going to be that without synchronization
就是没有同步
it will be wrong and with
这是错误的，并与
synchronization it will be slow and it's
同步会很慢，而且
just really an elegant anyway so if
反正真的很优雅
you'll want to avoid an accumulator we
您将要避免使用累加器
can use it we can use so-called reduce
可以使用它，我们可以使用所谓的减少
operation the one I'm going to look at
操作我要看的那个
here is that there's two overloads of of
这是的两个重载
reduce four-inch streams one of them
减少四英寸流之一
which takes a binary operator on int and
这需要int和
one of them which takes which which
其中之一需要哪个
takes a base value and a binary
需要一个基本值和一个二进制
operation on it we'll see the difference
对其进行操作，我们将看到差异
between them but the one I'm going to
他们之间，但我要去
look at is the first one now so avoiding
看是现在的第一个，所以避免
an accumulator you you would right you
一个蓄能器，你会纠正你的
could write something like this so here
可以写这样的东西，所以在这里
what we're doing is we are we're taking
我们正在做的是我们正在采取的
the the values and we're putting them
价值观，我们把它们
into a stream this is instead of using a
进入流，而不是使用
list here I'm just using an array and
在这里列出我只是在使用一个数组，
we're going to and we're going to reduce
我们将要减少
them over the over this summation
他们超过这个总和
operation what's that mean the a it
操作是什么意思
means that we're going to say that that
意味着我们要说
operation is going to take two in and
操作将需要两个
it's going to return the sum of them so
它会返回它们的总和，所以
the execution graph will look like that
执行图将如下所示
will look like the thing on the right
看起来像右边的东西
now and you can see that if obviously if
现在，您可以看到，如果
you scaled it up because this is
你扩大规模，因为这是
trivially small but if you had a if you
很小，但如果有的话
had a much larger array you can see that
有更大的阵列，您可以看到
you would get you would you would get a
你会得到你会得到一个
big gain in terms of they focus on a
他们专注于
single on a single variable so what's
在一个变量上是单变量，那是什么
the condition needed for this to work
工作所需的条件
well the answer is that
答案是
although that's one possible execution
虽然那是一种可能的执行
graph for this for that code it's not
该代码的图形不是
the only possible one so whether how the
唯一可能的一个
splitter ATAR works to divide the to
分割器ATAR致力于将
divide up the the array structure is
划分数组结构是
something that you can't really know in
你真的不知道的东西
advance so you shouldn't have to know
前进，所以您不必知道
the detail rather you should define an
细节，而你应该定义一个
operation that is going to work whether
即将进行的操作是否
it gets split and the condition for that
它分裂了，并且条件
to happen is that the it for example we
发生的是，例如我们
might get we might get this rather this
可能会得到我们可能会得到这个而不是这个
different this different execution graph
不同的这个不同的执行图
that's also possible and it's certainly
这也是可能的，当然
possible quite clearly if you if you
如果可能的话，可能会很清楚
were working with the with a sequential
正在与顺序
stream so the condition for it to for
流，所以它的条件
the condition that's required for this
为此所需的条件
for reduced to work is that the binary
对于减少工作是二进制
operator must be associative associative
运算符必须是关联的
means that that a plus B plus C has got
表示加B加C
to be the same as a a plus B plus C in
与aa加B加C相同
other words it doesn't matter how we
换句话说，我们如何都没关系
group things the order is still
整理东西仍然是顺序
important we're not talking about about
重要的是我们不是在谈论
things that operations that are
那个东西就是
reversible or commutative but we are
可逆或可交换，但我们
talking about we're talking about that
谈论我们在谈论那个
the way that we group operands to the
我们将操作数分组到的方式
operation that we supply to reduce has
我们提供的减少操作
got to be has got not not to matter so
一定要不要紧不要紧
you can see that if we scale this up now
您可以看到，如果我们现在扩大规模
we get it we get a better picture
我们知道了，我们得到了更好的画面
supposing we wanted to add together a
假设我们想将一个
lot of different things then you can see
很多不同的东西，那么你可以看到
that here you've got suppose you
假设你在这里
wouldn't we're imagining that this has
我们不是在想象这有
two threads this is executing on two
正在两个执行的两个线程
threads and and they can proceed
线程，他们可以继续
independently until at the end they're
直到最后他们独立
going to have to they're going to have
他们将不得不
to be the results are going to have to
结果是必须的
be joined together now you might think
现在在一起，你可能会想
well this is a huge overhead and a lot
好吧，这是巨大的开销，而且很多
of waste of time for just for doing
为了做而浪费时间
addition and you'd be quite right so
另外，你会很正确的
Regis so there's no way that reduction
瑞吉斯（Regis），所以没有减少的方法
it's actually going to win over over
实际上是要战胜
using an accumulator in terms of
在以下方面使用累加器
efficiency for simply for addition but
效率仅用于添加，但
if you if you have intermediate
如果你有中级水平
operations which which are more than
超过
just addition remember that remember
只要记住，记住
that what we've got here essentially is
我们在这里基本上是
that it's a pipeline I mean I've just
这是一条管道，我的意思是我只是
simplified it down to this very simple
简化为非常简单
to this very simple case but if you had
对于这个非常简单的情况，但是如果您有
a pipeline which was computationally
经过计算的管道
heavy and this is the important thing
沉重的，这是重要的
computationally expensive then in that
那么在计算上就很昂贵
case distributing that out over
案例分发出去
different
不同
cause and allowing them to proceed in
导致并允许他们继续前进
their processing could get your big gain
他们的处理可能会收获很大
so you'd serve for example if you're
因此，例如，如果您
doing cryptography calculations or if
进行密码计算或
you're writing a chess program or some
你在写象棋程序或一些
other thing that's going to require a
另一件事需要一个
lot of heavy computation then making the
很多繁重的计算，然后
maximum use of your parallel cores and
最大限度地利用并行核
nearly all machines now do have parallel
现在几乎所有机器都具有并行
course or server machines certainly do
当然还是服务器机器
that's going to be that's going to give
这将是给
you a that's going to give you a big
你会给你很大的
game and that's the that's the kind of
游戏，那就是那种
the underlying architectural motivation
潜在的建筑动机
towards towards towards this kind of
朝着这种
thing okay so so that's how a reduction
没关系，所以这就是减少
works arm primitives that's a very
适用于手臂原始体
simple case and reduction works on the
简单的案例和还原工作
immutable values to reference values as
不变值到参考值
well so and it's defined in the API so
很好，它是在API中定义的
I've shown I showed you reduced defined
我已经证明我给你减少了定义
on in streams and now I'm going to show
在流中，现在我要展示
you reduced defined on streams and you
您减少了对流的定义，而您
know we've got these four different
知道我们有这四个不同
kinds of streams the primitive ones in
原始流的种类
double and long and then we've got
加倍又长，然后我们得到
reference streams so they did define
参考流，所以他们确实定义了
reduction on reference streams and you
减少参考流，您
can see that it can sort of work so
可以看到它可以正常工作
there are not very many immutable value
不变的价值不是很多
table reference types in the platform
平台中的表引用类型
API but one of them is big decimal you
API，但其中之一是大十进制
can't you can't actually alter one of
你不能实际上不能改变其中之一
those and and so for example if you want
这些等等，例如，如果您想要
to add up a list of big decimal then or
加上一个大十进制的列表，然后
an array of big decimal then you can
一个大十进制数组，那么你可以
reduce then you can reduce them in that
减少然后您可以减少它们
kind of way but what about so that's
那种方式，那是怎么回事
immutable values but what about
不变的价值，那又如何
collections collections are not
集合不是
immutable well how can we can we reduce
一成不变的好，我们怎样才能减少
can we can we use reduction with
我们可以用
collections the API gives you to
API给您的集合
understand that because after all
明白，因为毕竟
they've defined the reduce operation on
他们已经定义了reduce操作
reference on reference values so it
参考参考值，所以
looks like it ought to work and in fact
看起来应该工作，实际上
the truth is that they didn't that they
事实是他们不是他们
there was a lot of time pressure on the
有很多时间的压力
definition of the of the stream
流的定义
framework and this was something which
框架，这是
if they'd have had more time to consider
如果他们有更多时间考虑
might well not that might well not have
可能没有，可能没有
slipped through not because it isn't you
溜走不是因为不是你
not because it's completely useless as I
不是因为像我这样完全没用
showed you in the bigdecimal example you
在十进制示例中向您展示了您
can use it but because it's
可以使用它，但是因为它是
very misleading and a lot of people have
误导很多人
fallen down down and out down a trap in
掉下来掉进陷阱
this case well there is one way in which
这种情况下，有一种方法
you could make reduction to collections
你可以减少收藏
work and that way is kind of pretty
工作，这种方式很漂亮
horrible you could take each element of
可怕的是你可能会接受
your stream and you could and in the
你的流，你可以和在
client code you could create a new empty
客户代码，您可以创建一个新的空白
collection and then you could submit
收集，然后您可以提交
that and then you could submit those
那你可以提交那些
collections to the to the just for a
收集到的只是一个
reduction and the reduction operation
归约和归约运算
would be a doll that a dormer just
会是一个天窗娃娃
merges two collections together it's
将两个集合合并在一起
it's possible to do that and I will show
有可能做到这一点，我将展示
you an example at the very end of of
你是一个例子的结尾
doing it but it's not something you
这样做，但这不是你的事
would ever want to do in practice it's
会想在实践中做到的
really it's really it's really pretty
真的，真的，真的很漂亮
grim
严峻
it's it's extremely and if it's going to
这是极端的，如果要
be extremely inefficient because you're
效率极低，因为您
gonna have to create lots and lots of
将不得不创造很多
extra objects and you're gonna have to
多余的东西，你将不得不
use a door which is typically all the
使用通常是所有的门
time which is typically much more
时间通常要多得多
inefficient than the add operation on
比添加操作效率低
collections and basically it's horrible
收集，基本上是可怕的
so we can do better so over an identity
所以我们可以做得更好
alright so I just wanted to say that's
好吧，我只想说那是
right before I go on to talk about about
就在我继续谈论之前
collection so I just want to look at the
收集，所以我只想看看
over at the other overload I've talked
在我谈论过的另一个超载
about the about the reduction method
关于约简法
that takes a single operator well what
只需一个操作员
about the one which takes a base value
关于一个具有基本值的
and handin operator so that's going to
和handin运算符，以便
be important for what we took for what
对于我们采取的措施很重要
we talk about next and we've got those
我们接下来要谈的是
both for both primitive streams as well
两者都适用于原始流
as in the top and for reference streams
如顶部和参考流
as in as in the lower example there and
就像下面的例子一样
you can see an example here where in the
您可以在此处看到一个示例
code I'm calculating the sum there of
我正在计算代码的总和
over an array of bigdecimal
在一个十进制数组上
and the way that I'm doing it is by
而我做的方式是
reducing over big decimal zero as the as
减少大十进制零作为
the base value and then and then each
基本值，然后再分别
and then each successive operation will
然后每个后续操作将
be will will be add and now that works
将将被添加，现在可以正常工作
and it that works in a particularly
它在特别是
useful way because it means you don't
有用的方法，因为这意味着您不会
have to return an optional you know that
必须返回一个可选的，你知道
even if the stream
即使流
empty we had an optional in the past in
空，过去我们有一个可选的
the previous example from the from the
来自的上一个示例
other overload you can see optional int
其他重载，您可以看到可选的int
and optional of T on the slide but for
和可选的幻灯片上的T，但
this one you don't need to have an
这个你不需要
optional because even if the stream is
可选，因为即使流是
empty you know that you know there's
空的你知道你知道那里
going to be at least one value one value
将至少是一个值一个值
is going to come back because you
会回来的，因为你
because you've got big decimal zero to
因为你有大十进制零
start off with so that so this works so
以这样开始
this works for immutable objects fine
这适用于不可变的对象
and and this is what it looks like
这就是它的样子
reduction over an identity looks like
减少身份看起来像
this now so we've got a we've got our to
现在，所以我们有一个我们有我们要
the two halves of the potentially much
潜在的两半
more than two but the two halves of the
超过两个，但两个半
array here and we and each thread is
数组在这里，我们和每个线程都是
what it's going to do operating on the
它在操作上将要做什么
separate core it's going to start off in
单独的核心，它将开始于
the case of it in the case of our big
在我们大的情况下
decimal here it's going to start off
小数点在这里开始
with the zero and then it's going to add
与零，然后将其添加
the values sequentially when it's
当它是
finished doing that bit when it's do it
完成时就完成了
when it's finished doing that and when
什么时候完成的
all the threats have finished doing that
所有的威胁已经完成了
they can merge the results together will
他们可以将结果合并在一起
this work with collections
这项工作与收藏
well reduction over an identity doesn't
很好地简化身份不会
work with collections at all why not
完全与馆藏合作，为什么不呢？
no not immutable but I only but I was
不是不是一成不变的，但我只是但我是
the one who said that this should only
那个说这应该只
work with them you too if you try to do
如果您尝试与他们一起工作
reduction over collections you'll not
减少您不会收集的收藏
get a compile error or anything you'll
出现编译错误或其他任何错误
not get an you'll not get an execution
不得到你就不会被执行
error that we know it won't throw an
我们知道它不会抛出错误的错误
exception or anything like that but
例外或类似的东西，但
you'll just get the wrong answer
你只会得到错误的答案
well supposing it supposing I provide
好吧，假设我提供
supposing and providers so the question
假设和提供者等问题
so the question is is it
所以问题是
non-deterministic because I don't have a
没有确定性，因为我没有
starting value but suppose I provided an
初始值，但假设我提供了一个
empty collection same ways I provided a
空集合我提供的方式相同
big decimal zero there and then to
大十进制零那里然后
collection for the starting point does
起点集合
ordering matter ordering ordering will
订购事项订购命令
influence the result yes absolutely but
绝对会影响结果，但是
it's not actually that it's not the key
其实这不是关键
so depending on what on what order the
所以根据什么顺序
the threads execute you will get
执行线程，您将得到
different results in a quite an
在相当不同的结果
unpredictable way I touched the cable oh
变幻莫测的方式我摸了索哦
no I touch the cable we're done but at
不，我触摸了我们完成的电缆，但是在
least at least I've got a discussion
至少至少我有一个讨论
point anyway to go on with all I did
无论如何要继续我所做的一切
this it's just a merest brush so the
这只是一个最简单的刷子，所以
problem is with the this is a real
问题是这是一个真实的
example of multi processing can I do
我可以做多处理的例子
this so the the the reason why it won't
这就是为什么它不会的原因
work is because the Assumption behind
工作是因为背后的假设
reduction is that the is that the base
减少的是基础
the base value is if you that the
基本值是
assumptions the base value is immutable
假设基值是不变的
I just read really carefully
我只是认真阅读
it's a game isn't it
这是一个游戏，不是吗
the the assumptions of the base that the
该基础的假设
base value is immutable so that point
基本值是不可变的，因此
about immutability is really important
关于不变性真的很重要
so basically each thread is going to try
所以基本上每个线程都会尝试
to use the same the same base value for
使用相同的基本值
it's going to try to use the same base
它将尝试使用相同的基数
value for for its computation so what
计算的价值，那么
will happen is if you say I'm gonna if
会发生的是，如果你说我要
you offer it if you offer it a a an
如果你提供它，你提供它
empty collection if you say the empty
如果您说的是空集合
collection is to be the start of this
收集将是这个的开始
reduction then every thread will take
减少，那么每个线程都会占用
that same collection as I start of the
和我开始时一样的收藏
reduction and it'll be empty to start
减少，开始将是空的
off with but when the second thread
关闭，但当第二个线程
comes along it won't be empty any longer
随之而来的将不再是空的
but the second thread won't know that so
但是第二个线程不知道
the threads will get quite confused and
线程会变得很混乱，
I'll get they'll make concurrent access
我将让他们进行并发访问
to that collection so it won't work it
到那个集合，所以它不起作用
won't work it doesn't matter well it
不会工作没关系吧
probably will work let me think of it
可能会起作用，让我想起来
let me think from home will it work on
让我想在家中可以使用
us on a single thread it doesn't yeah
我们在一个线程上不是吗
it probably it probably will work on a
它可能会在一个
single thread if you're lucky but if the
单线程，如果您很幸运，但是如果
but absolutely the way that the the way
但绝对是这样的
that the API is specified is it says
指定的API是说
absolutely you not guaranteed to have it
绝对您不保证拥有它
work you're not guarantees so at some
您无法保证工作，所以在某些情况下
point in the future when somebody says
指向未来，当有人说
ah this program looks like it might run
嗯，这个程序看起来好像可以运行
better on parallel hardware your program
在程序的并行硬件上更好
will break I mean your program is
会打破我的意思是你的程序是
absolutely not thread safe and it will
绝对不是线程安全的，它将
take very little change in how it in how
在如何做方面几乎没有改变
its even and how its deployed possibly
它的均匀性以及如何部署
in the future and deploy lots of
在未来并部署大量
different hardware and it might break so
不同的硬件，它可能会因此中断
you so it so it's not it's not it's not
你，所以这不是，不是，不是
the road to go down we've got to do
走下去的路我们必须做
better than that and so the answer to
比这更好，所以答案
this is the answer this is collectors
这就是答案，这就是收藏家
and the idea here is that instead of
这里的想法是，而不是
supplying an identity a base value we
为身份提供基本价值
supply a function so the function is
提供功能，因此该功能是
executed by each thread and it produces
由每个线程执行，并产生
a new fresh empty collection on each
每个都有一个新的新鲜空集合
occasion so so it's a in this case it's
有时所以在这种情况下是
a lambda of the I'm imagining it so that
我在想像中的lambda
for this particular collectable code
对于此特定的可收集代码
whatever it is it's a lambda which takes
不管它是lambda
no arguments it's a supplier when they
毫无疑问，他们是供应商
in the language of the stream API it's
用流API的语言
the lambda function API it says it's a
lambda函数API它说这是一个
supplier which takes no arguments and
没有争议的供应商
returns something in this case an empty
在这种情况下返回空
and empty collection and if you eat
和空的收藏，如果你吃
thread calls that when it when it starts
线程在启动时调用它
work then each one is obviously going to
工作，那么每个人显然都会去
get its own separate new fresh thread in
获得自己的单独新线程
the new fresh collection so there isn't
新的新系列，所以没有
reduce overload that looks like this but
减少看起来像这样的过载，但是
it uses an identity and not a supplier
它使用身份而不是供应商
it's very similar but it's just a
这非常相似，但这只是一个
warning to you that if you ever if you
警告您，如果您曾经
ever are trying to do reduction over
曾经试图减少
over over stream don't and you're trying
过流不，而您正在尝试
to reduce onto mutable values the
减少到可变值
reduction doesn't work and that's really
减少无效，这确实是
the reason why the API should maybe have
API应该具有的原因
a warning in it or something like that
警告或类似的东西
but hey we don't do that with Java guys
但是嘿，我们不和Java家伙一起做
and we don't put warnings in the API
而且我们不会在API中添加警告
documentation but we really but we
文档，但我们确实但我们
really should in this case so that's so
在这种情况下真的应该如此
this is the answer now we've got these
这就是答案，现在我们有了这些
things now we we've seen the components
现在我们已经看到了组件
of a collector here we've got the
这里的收藏家
supplier in blue we've got an
蓝色的供应商，我们有一个
accumulator which which so-called which
所谓哪个蓄电池
adds
添加
elements to to a container and then
元素到容器，然后
we've got we've got the the end when we
当我们结束时，我们已经结束了
when we the each thread is calculated
当我们计算每个线程时
all the values it's going to calculate
它要计算的所有值
the results have to be joined together
结果必须结合在一起
in something called a combiner so that
在所谓的组合器中
and that is what that is what what we're
那就是我们所要的
looking at is define a collector you
看着是定义一个收藏家
need to provide all these three things a
需要提供所有这三样东西
supplier an accumulator and the combiner
提供累加器和组合器
and that makes it sound like it's gonna
这听起来像是
be really hard and already you're sort
真的很努力，已经很合理了
of thinking this is too much for me but
想这对我来说太多了
don't think that because I'm kind of
不要以为是因为我有点
broke I've sort of broken the rule
我违反了规则
really here and it was a rule that that
真的在这里，这是一个规则
Brian gets was very emphatic when I was
我那时，布莱恩（Brian）非常强调
writing the book he said don't tell
写他说不告诉的书
people about this stuff he said because
人们对这个东西他说，因为
he was very concerned that it would look
他非常担心它看起来
hard and he said I want them to
努力，他说我要他们
understand it's really very easy we
明白我们真的很容易
don't actually have to define collectors
实际上不必定义收集器
of our own very often at all there's a
我们自己经常有一个
vast array of a vast number of of
大量的
collector sort of given to us by factory
收藏家按工厂提供给我们的
methods in the collectors class and
收藏家类中的方法和
those are what I'm going to spend most
这些是我要花费最多的
of today talking about because they're
今天谈论，因为他们是
really useful and they save you from
真的很有用，它们可以使您免受
having to do this work nearly all the
几乎必须要做这项工作
time and I will talk at the end about
时间，我将在最后谈论
writing your own collector but it's not
写自己的收藏家，但不是
something you have to do you have to do
你必须要做的事情
very often okay so so that's the the
通常很多，所以这就是
basic motivation behind the behind
背后的基本动机
what's going on with collectors and now
藏家现在怎么回事
I'm going to talk about a bit about
我将谈论一些有关
using the predefined collectors that
使用预定义的收集器
this is really kind of the heart of the
这真的是
talk in a way apart from the practical
说话与实际不符
work that we're going to do this is this
我们要做的工作是这样的
is the heart of the the information so
是信息的心脏，所以
the collectors API is provides these
收藏家API提供了这些
factory methods in the collectors class
收藏家类中的工厂方法
they produce standalone collectors and
他们生产独立的收藏家，
I'm going to that not all the collectors
我要去的不是所有的收藏家
are standalone some of them are only for
是独立的，其中一些仅用于
use as downstream collectors and I'll
用作下游收藏家，我会
explain that in a little while but in
解释一下，但是在
the first place let's look at these
首先让我们看看这些
things that are standalone collectors
独立收藏家的东西
because they're easier to understand
因为它们更容易理解
they are and though I'm going to say
他们是，尽管我要说
they fall into three categories
他们分为三类
once the ones that will collect into
一旦将收集到
framework supplied containers ones that
框架提供的容器
all collect into custom collections
全部收集到自定义收藏中
where you where you supply the
您在哪里提供
collection yourself and think that
收集自己并认为
something I'm that I call classification
我称之为分类的东西
maps which are the ones that are
那些是
actually most versatile and useful
实际上最通用，最有用
so the predefined collectors are kind of
所以预定义的收集器是
straightforward they come from factory
他们直接来自工厂
methods as well from factory methods in
方法以及工厂方法
the collectors class these factory
收藏家给这些工厂上课
methods I'm not going to be writing
我不会写的方法
collectors dr. lists and collectors dr.
收藏家博士名单和收藏家博士。
set because it would make the slides
设置，因为它将使幻灯片
unreadable but anytime you see you see
不可读，但任何时候看到
methods like this this is this is what
像这样的方法，这就是
they are they come from the they come
他们是他们来自他们
from that class and they and the the and
从那一类，他们和
sorry the the top line the top line of
对不起，顶行
these are these things which will which
这些就是这些
the frameworks provides the supplier in
框架向供应商提供
the case of two lists it it was it will
在两个列表的情况下，它将是
currently it will collect into a into an
目前它将收集到一个
ArrayList not guarantee that is always
ArrayList不保证总是
will no part of the specification but
将不属于规范的一部分，但
that's what it does and a hash set and a
这就是它的作用，还有一个哈希集和一个
hash map again not not not define
哈希图再次不是没有定义
joining is slightly different
加盟略有不同
what joining does is it can helpfully
加入的好处是可以有帮助
concatenate strings so it does things
连接字符串，以便执行操作
like it concatenate strings with putting
喜欢它把字符串连接在一起
interspersing commas between them if you
如果您之间插入逗号，
want or some other separator rather than
想要或其他分隔符而不是
you're having to do this clumsy thing
你必须做这笨拙的事情
that we always used to have to do of
我们过去经常要做的
iterating over them then taking the last
遍历他们然后拿最后一个
separator off so it does that and then
分离出它，然后这样做
will allow you to specify a prefix and
将允许您指定前缀和
the suffix and so forth so joining falls
后缀，依此类推
into this category it's this way I
进入这个类别，我就是这样
talked about containers rather than
谈论容器而不是
collections because the idea of a
集合，因为一个想法
collector is collecting into something
收藏家正在收集东西
that will hold the result really rather
这将真正保持结果
than rather than always a collection it
而不是总是收藏它
often is in the the to map and to
通常是在地图和
collection are will allow you to specify
集合将允许您指定
your own kind of maps but you want a a
你自己的地图，但是你想要一个
tree map or a linked hash map say or
树图或链接的哈希图说或
something like that or supposing you
这样的事情或假设你
want your collecting to a deck or some
希望您将收集到甲板或一些
other some other things that that
其他一些其他的东西
implements the array deck some other
其他实现数组平台
things that implements the java.util
实现java.util的东西
collection so the user would probably so
收集，因此用户可能会这样
you would provide it the supplier in
您可以提供给供应商
that case and then last of all these
这种情况，然后是所有这些的最后
things that produce classification maps
产生分类图的东西
and will be looking a lot at those so
将会非常关注这些
I'm going to illustrate how these things
我将说明这些事情
work with with animations which are kind
处理善良的动画
of start off looking a bit a bit over
开始看起来有点过头了
simple and you'll think I'm insulting
简单，你会觉得我很侮辱
your intelligence but they do get a bit
你的智慧，但他们确实有一点
harder here's an example of what would
更难的是这是一个例子
happen if you wanted to collect the all
如果您想收集全部，就会发生
the elements of the person stream
人流的元素
into into a into a set so the the code
变成一个成一个这样的代码
the code is at the bottom collectors
代码在底部的收集器中
doctor set and and the my idea of the
医生设置和我的想法
animation is the thing on the left is a
动画是左边的东西
is it's going to be a stream and the
这将是一条小溪，
person objects will come along it and
人对象会随之而来，
and then and what will be emitted at the
然后，在
right-hand side is whatever we're trying
右边就是我们要尝试的
to get so in this case it's pretty
在这种情况下很漂亮
simple the the collector creates so it
收集器创建的简单，因此
creates a hash set object and internally
创建一个哈希集对象并在内部
and that and it puts each of the
那，它把每个
elements that come down the stream into
顺流而下的元素
into that into that hash set object and
进入那个哈希集对象
then when the stream is exhausted at the
然后当流在
end when the automatically it perceives
当它自动感知时结束
that the stream is exhausted and then
溪流已耗尽，然后
and then the set then the set is emitted
然后集合然后发出集合
so that's pretty straightforward
所以这很简单
mmm the and I won't insult your
嗯，我不会侮辱你的
intelligence by showing you the same
通过向您展示相同的知识
thing about to list because it's kind of
之所以要列出，是因为
obvious but maybe to map is slightly
明显，但也许到地图稍微
more interesting because to map takes
更有趣，因为地图需要
take two functions it a function which
有两个功能
is going to provide the keys for the for
将提供用于的密钥
the entries of the map and a function
地图条目和函数
that's going to provide the values so in
这将提供值，因此
this case we want a map from city for
在这种情况下，我们想要一张来自城市的地图
for all of the for all of the persons in
对于所有的人
for all the person objects and people we
对于所有的人对象和人，我们
want a map that's going to that's that's
想要一张要去的地图就是
going to for each city give the
去每个城市给
correspondent given the name of a person
通讯员给出一个人的名字
of the person who lives there so the way
这样住在那里的人
that works is like this again again it's
再次起作用是这样的
it's kind of this kind of simple bill
这种简单的账单
comes in bill lives in where's bill live
进账单生活在哪里住账单
he lives in London so London becomes the
他住在伦敦，所以伦敦成为
the the key for that for that entry and
该条目的密钥，并且
and Bill's name is surprisingly bill and
比尔的名字叫比尔
so that becomes the value for that for
这样就成为了
that entry and now here comes a me and
该条目，现在是我和
Amy lives in Athens and and her name is
艾米住在雅典，她的名字叫
also Amy so in this way we're building
还有艾米，所以我们用这种方式
we build a map up and and in due course
我们建立了地图，并在适当的时候
these stream is exhausted and that map
这些流用尽了，那张地图
comes out we get a map from city to
出来后，我们会得到一张从城市到
string because because the key mapper
字符串，因为因为键映射器
producer took a person and gave a city
制片人带一个人给了一个城市
and the value mapping took a person and
价值映射花了一个人，
and give a string so that's that seems
并给出一个字符串，这似乎是
pretty that seems pretty straightforward
看起来很简单
but what happens though I mean you can
但是会发生什么，尽管我是说你可以
probably see any meat a snake coming up
可能看到蛇有肉
straight away and what happens if two
马上，如果两个
people live in the same city pun you
人们住在同一个城市双关语
will get it you will indeed get it
会得到的，你的确会得到的
collisions here's John and now John has
发生冲突，这里是约翰，现在约翰
moved to Athens what's going to happen
搬到雅典将会发生什么事
there well you can't have two to map
那里你不可能有两个地图
entries with this with the same key
具有相同键的条目
obviously so it by default what you'll
显然，因此默认情况下您会
get is an illegal state exception you
get是一个非法的州例外
might not be bothered about that because
可能不会对此感到困扰，因为
after all you might actually have a data
毕竟您实际上可能有数据
set where you actually knew that
设定您实际知道的地方
everybody was going to be in it that all
每个人都将融入其中
the keys were going to be distinct but
按键将是不同的，但
it but there's another overload which
它，但是还有另一个过载
allows for the possibility that this
允许这种可能性
situation might arise and you might want
情况可能会出现，您可能想要
to handle it so this one takes has the
处理它，所以这个需要
key mapped on the value map as before
像以前一样将键映射到值映射上
but now it also wants a merge function
但现在它也想要合并功能
and the merge function takes two two
合并功能需要两个
values and two values in the value
值和值中的两个值
domain and does something with them and
域，并与他们做一些事情，
gives you back a value in the value
给您带来价值中的价值
domain so in this case I very simply and
域，所以在这种情况下，我非常简单地
what I've done is I've taken the two two
我所做的是我拿了两个两个
strings and I've concatenated them
字符串，我将它们串联在一起
together just to be just just for the
在一起只是为了
simplicity of the example and now you
简单的例子，现在你
can see that if that code is executed
可以看到该代码是否已执行
and and and it turns out that Amy and
事实证明，艾米和
John live in the same place then here
约翰和这里住在同一地方
comes here comes John now we've got the
来这里来约翰，现在我们有
same collision and in this case what
同样的碰撞，在这种情况下，
happens is since we've got the since the
发生的是因为我们有了
lambda at the bottom which takes the two
底部有两个lambda
string values and joins them together
字符串值并将它们连接在一起
that's what's going to be put in to the
这就是要放入的内容
to the value of that entry in the case
达到该条目的值
of that collision so that's what's going
碰撞的原因就是这样
to appear so I should say the reason the
出现，所以我应该说原因
reason why I go through all of that is
我经历所有这些的原因是
when when you first of all see the
当您首先看到
signatures like at the top there and
像顶部的签名
they get the I mean that's getting a bit
他们得到了我的意思是这有点
complicated and they get a lot more
复杂，他们得到更多
complicated and if you're not used to
复杂，如果您不习惯
this ap I know when I first met it IV
我第一次见面时就知道了
some no there's a lot of angle brackets
有些不，有很多尖括号
there really is and and there's a
确实存在，并且有一个
naturally in there in the real API
自然就在真正的API中
there's quite a lot of question marks
有很多问号
which I've taped which I've edited out
我已经录音的内容
of the slides for simplicity so it's
为了简单起见，
quite off-putting and
颇有争议
and I think it's quite a good idea to
我认为这是一个很好的主意
just you know to maybe to get over to
只要你知道也许可以克服
you that what's going on behind the
你那背后发生了什么
scenes is actually really a lot more
场景实际上要多得多
simple so that's just right so that's
简单，这就是正确，所以
the framework that's the one that does
就是那个框架
the framework supplied containers and
框架提供了容器和
that's them they're custom collections
就是他们，他们是自定义收藏
is pretty is pretty straightforward
很漂亮很简单
there's there's a to map method here
这里有一个映射方法
which is going to which is going to
这将要去哪
allow you to to collect talk to a custom
允许您收集与自定义的对话
map I've taken the example here of a
地图我在这里以一个例子
tree map you notice that the because of
树状图，您注意到，因为
they're all the difficulties that we now
他们都是我们现在遇到的困难
encounter with overloading overloading
遇到过载过载
produces more method overloading
产生更多方法重载
producing more and more difficulties as
产生越来越多的困难
time goes by and the language is
时间流逝，语言是
extended so it gave a lot of problems
扩展，所以带来了很多问题
with lambdas and method references and
带有lambda和方法引用，以及
so now they it's a fashion in API is to
所以现在它们在API中很流行
not define to not define two methods
不定义不定义两种方法
with the same number of arguments so
具有相同数量的参数
that so that for example here although
这样，例如这里
you probably you may well not want to
你可能你可能不想
merge function you're still going to
您仍然要合并的功能
have to supply motor function if you
如果您必须提供电动机功能
want to supply a map supplier because it
想要提供地图供应商，因为它
because the if we left out the merge
因为如果我们忽略合并
function just allowed you to supply them
功能只是让您提供它们
at the map function only we'd have to
在Map函数上，我们只需要
met two overloads each with four
遇到两个过载，每个过载四个
arguments and then method overloading
参数，然后方法重载
starts to become very difficult so we're
开始变得非常困难，所以我们
playing an easy way now so you have to
现在玩一个简单的方法，所以您必须
supply an emerge function but of course
提供新兴功能，但当然
if you don't really want one if you
如果你真的不想要一个
don't really want to one then you can
真的不想要一个那么你可以
just go back to the default which is to
只需返回默认值即可
throw an illegal state exception so what
抛出非法状态异常
about this map Factory well I haven't
关于这张地图我还没有工厂
got an animation for this but the idea
为此有一个动画，但是这个主意
is that basically it works in exactly
基本上是完全可以
the same way as I as the as a previous
和我以前一样
map example shirt did but in this case
地图示例衬衫没有，但在这种情况下
you are telling the the the collector
你告诉收藏家
what to put as the container that it's
作为容器放置什么
collecting into so you see you you give
收集到所以你看到你给
it what it'll do it it was call the
它会做什么它被称为
supplier that you provide in this case
您在这种情况下提供的供应商
we supplied the the the supplier we gave
我们提供了我们给的供应商
was that was a parameterless constructor
那是一个无参数的构造函数
of tree map and so it will call that get
树图的地图，因此它将调用
a tree map and it will and it will use
树状图，它将并且将使用
that as the box that it's going to
作为盒子
there's going to collect into
将会收集到
it does indeed sorry because so the
它的确确实很抱歉，因为这样
question is at the end does it have to
问题是到底有没有必要
combine the multiple multiple tree maps
结合多个多个树图
that it's created yes absolutely so it
它是绝对创建的，所以它
has no map merge at the end and it has
最后没有地图合并，并且有
to do that in a thread safe way because
以线程安全的方式做到这一点，因为
tree map of course is not it's not so
树形图当然不是，不是
it's safe so that one of the big bonuses
这是安全的，所以其中的一大奖励
of the of the stream API is that it
流API的特征在于
allows you to use parallel streams and
允许您使用并行流和
do parallel processing collecting into
做并行处理收集到
collection containers that are not
不收集容器
themselves thread safe and it manages
自己线程安全，并且可以管理
the thread safety for you but obviously
线程安全为您服务，但显然
there's a cost and I mean the cost is
有一个成本，我的意思是成本是
really quite high for example emerging
真的很高，例如新兴
tree Maps that's a really quite an
树形地图非常
expensive operation but but it's safe
昂贵的操作，但是很安全
it'll do that safely that's defined so
它会安全地定义
so there's two characters the two
所以两个有两个字符
methods for collecting two custom
收集两个自定义方法
containers one of them is the one of
容器之一是其中之一
them is for custom maps because of
它们用于自定义地图，因为
course maps don't implement the Java
课程地图未实现Java
util collection interface but everything
util收集界面，但一切
else does or queues and sets and this
否则做或排队和设置，这
all implement the the the collection
全部实现集合
interface and so the so the method for
界面等等，方法
that provides you with that will allow
为您提供的将允许
you to to collect to a collection looks
您要收集到一个集合看起来
like this that's the signature but the
像这样是签名，但是
but the the parametric type see is as
但是参数类型看到的是
defined as being it has to be it has to
被定义为必须
be a subtype of collection and and and
是collection的子类型，并且and
what that returns is a collector which
返回的是一个收集器
will take I should have I should have
需要我拥有
said something about the the arguments
说了一些论点
to the the type arguments to the
的类型参数
collector the the first one is the type
收藏家的第一个是类型
that's being collected the last one is
被收集的最后一个是
the type that is being collected too so
这样收集的类型也是如此
so I mean typically for us it would have
所以我的意思是通常对我们来说
been like a person and list of person
就像一个人和一个人的名单
and the one in the middle is an
中间的一个是
intermediate type which is used
使用的中间类型
internally within the within the
内部内部
collector it's there's a there's an
收藏家那里有一个
extra stage that I haven't told you
我没有告诉过你的额外舞台
about that happens at the point in which
关于这一点发生在
the values are emitted so it's called a
值被发射出来，所以叫做
finisher and once all the values have
整理器，一旦所有值都具有
been collected together something
被收集在一起的东西
sometimes has to be done
有时必须要做
to them in order to in order for them to
为了他们
be emitted
被发射
the simplest example that would
最简单的例子
immediately come to your mind is if you
立即想到的是，如果您
had a if you're using a stringbuilder
如果您使用的是stringbuilder，则有一个
internally to build a string up but
内部建立一个字符串，但
you're actually what you wanted to
你实际上就是你想要的
return was a string so the finish are
返回是一个字符串，所以完成是
there well that would would do that
在那里，那将会做到
would do that job usually you don't have
会做你通常没有的工作
to worry about that about that middle
担心那个中间
type parameter because unless you're
类型参数，因为除非您
writing your own collectors it's not
写自己的收藏家不是
usually very important so the reason I
通常很重要，所以我的原因
laid out the that's the method
布局就是方法
definition of to collection is because
对集合的定义是因为
if you see that in the in the API
如果您在API中看到了
documentation if anybody still looks at
如果有人还在看文档
API documentation of course I'm an
我当然是API文档
old-fashioned person then it looks
老式的人，然后看起来
pretty menacing but actually it all fits
险恶，但实际上很合适
it does all fit together here's the
它确实适合在一起的
example of of using two collections
使用两个集合的示例
supposing we wanted to collect not to a
假设我们想不收集
tree map but to a tree set while tree
树图，但树设置为树
set is just to kind of set and so it
设置只是一种设置，所以它
implements the the the collection job
实施收集工作
util collection interface and here what
util收集界面，这里是什么
we're doing is we're making it as we're
我们正在做的就是我们正在做
going to get and a set of sorted named a
将要获得的一组命名为
set of names but we want it to be sorted
名称集，但我们希望对其进行排序
we wanted to be created sorted if you
我们想被创建排序如果
put things into a tree set then they'll
把东西放到树上然后他们会
be sorted on their natural order in the
按其自然顺序排序
usual in the case of strings that's
通常在字符串的情况下
their alphabetic order in the usual way
他们的字母顺序通常
of things so so this code will give you
的东西，所以这段代码会给你
back a set of a set of a set of the
背一组一组
names of the person objects and in
人员对象的名称和
people sorted by alphabetically so
人们按字母顺序排序
that's the first two types frameworks
那是前两种类型的框架
supplied containers and custom and
提供的容器和定制和
custom collections and the third type is
自定义集合，第三个类型是
classification Maps so these these are
分类图，这些是
all created by by grouping by also by
全部通过分组也通过分组
grouping by concurrent and and
按并发和和分组
partitioning by both there's that's not
通过两者进行分区不是
very important grouping by is really
非常重要的分组依据是
that really the one that matters we've
那真的是我们重要的
got three kinds we've got simple ones
有三种我们有简单的
that with downstream or the downstream
与下游或下游
and a map Factory let's have a look at
和地图工厂让我们看一下
these
这些
so here's grouping by with a with a
所以这里是用
classifier the idea this is it'll make a
分类器的想法，这将使
classification mapping it's sort of like
分类映射有点像
to map except that the values that are
映射，除了
placed in the map are our lists of
放在地图上的是我们的清单
elements our lists that
元素我们的清单
I should say the big the big l1 list
我应该说大名单
corresponding to each classification key
对应于每个分类键
so for example if you use person get
例如，如果您使用person get
city as the as the as the classifier
城市作为分类器
then you would get a map from city to a
然后您会得到一张从城市到城市的地图
list of person and that would associate
与之相关的人的清单
each person that would associate each
每个会联系每个人的人
city with the put the people that lived
放着生活的人的城市
in that city and the code the code for
在那个城市和代码的代码
doing that would look like what you see
这样做看起来就像您看到的一样
at the bottom there
在底部
people got stream clicked collectors
人们得到流点击收藏家
grouping by and that means that what
分组，这意味着什么
we're going to do is we're going to
我们要做的是
apply that that function that method
将该函数应用于该方法
person get city I'm going to apply that
人得到城市，我要申请
to each person object as it comes
面对每个人的对象
through and then we're going to and
通过，然后我们将去
we're going to use the result as a key
我们将使用结果作为关键
and we're going to take the we're going
我们将采取我们要
to take the person object and add it to
拿人对象并将其添加到
a list of list of persons that
名单的人，
correspond to that so here's a bit of
对应于此，所以这里有点
his how that's going to work in a in an
他如何在一个
animation so we bill and John live in
动画，所以我们和Bill住在一起
London and Amy lives in Athens now
伦敦和艾米现在住在雅典
they're moving about these people so
他们正在四处寻找这些人
bill so bill comes in bill lives in
账单，所以账单进来
London and so he gets put into he gets
伦敦，所以他被投入
put into a list of person objects
放入人员对象列表
associated with London and Amy comes in
与伦敦和艾米相关的进来
and Amy goes to a is added to a list of
艾米（Amy）前往并被添加到
persons that they're associated with
与他们相关的人
Athens and John comes in and kind of
雅典和约翰进来，有点
obviously joanna is going to be added to
显然乔安娜将被添加到
the list the bill is in and now the
帐单所在的清单，现在
stream is exhausted and that and we've
流已经精疲力尽，而我们
got and we get out the map from city to
得到了，我们得到了从城市到
listen to the list of person so that
听人的名单，以便
seems pretty straightforward and
似乎很简单，
possibly quite useful we'll see ways in
可能非常有用，我们将在
which it's quite useful but it but quite
这是非常有用的，但是
limited so like what if you didn't want
有限，所以就像如果你不想那样
to put them into a list every time
每次都将它们放入列表
suppose you want to do something more
假设你想做更多的事情
with them one of the things that I've
和他们在一起，我曾经做过的一件事
said about the that I haven't said about
说了我没说过的
the great virtues of the Collector's API
收藏家API的优点
is that it's very composable so you can
是非常可组合的，所以您可以
we're going to see how you can fit
我们将看看你如何适应
different collectors together and build
不同的收藏家一起建立
up quite a complicated quite a complex
相当复杂相当复杂
and elaborate processing pipeline just
并精心制作处理流程
by fitting them together so we'll see
通过将它们放在一起，我们将看到
how that works this is this is this is
这是怎么工作的这是这个
the start of it supposing you wanted to
假设您想开始
suppose you wanted to
假设你想
make something other than a list maybe
做出除清单以外的内容
you wanted to make it maybe you wanted
你想做到，也许你想
to make a set instead well there is this
做一个集，而不是好有这个
idea of a downstream collector so a
下游收集器的想法
downstream collector is one which takes
下游收集器是需要
the values that have been that been
一直以来的价值
emitted from from a collector and it
从收集器发射出来的
within the same collector a does some
在同一个收集器中做一些
further work on them so you get an age
对它们进行进一步的工作，使您有年龄
of clip of collection work so so if you
收集工作的片段，所以如果您
sort of the overload of grouping by
分组的重载
which takes a classifier and the
这需要一个分类器和
downstream collector uses the classifier
下游收集器使用分类器
function to make a classification
进行分类的功能
mapping into a container which is
映射到一个容器中
defined by a downstream collectors and
由下游收集者定义
another stage goes on so it's so so the
下一阶段正在进行，所以如此
values placed in the map are containers
放置在地图中的值是容器
of the elements and one container
元素和一个容器
corresponds to each classification key
对应于每个分类键
so if we wanted to get a set of person
所以如果我们想找一个人
rather than a list of person we would we
而不是我们会列出的人
would use the we would use a downstream
将使用我们将使用下游
collector to set remember to set is a
收藏家设置记得设置是一个
factory method of the collectors class
收藏家的工厂方法
which which creates a collector for you
这为您创建了一个收集器
so it's so there's like as a collector
所以就像有收藏家一样
embedded inside of this collector here's
嵌入此收集器的内部
that here's the diagram did you see the
这是图，您看到了吗
downstream collector is actually
下游收集器实际上是
embedded inside of this this outer
嵌入此外部的内部
collector and his in his how it's going
收藏家和他的情况
to work bill comes in and he goes and
工作法案进来，他去了，
and he and he gets clattered he gets put
他和他变得手足无措
into not not that not a list as before
不像以前那样不是一个列表
which was automatic which was the
这是自动的
automatic default but into whatever were
自动默认，但无论如何
into whatever container has been defined
放入已定义的任何容器中
by the downstream collector and and and
由下游收集器和
in this case it's to set so you can see
在这种情况下，要进行设置，以便您可以看到
these are like little little versions of
这些就像小小的版本
the to set collector that I started off
我开始的设置收集器
with and then and and then so on with
然后再然后再以
the rest of them the name Ian and and
他们其余的人叫伊恩和
John so actually you might say well like
约翰，所以实际上你可能会说得很好
how does this relate to the to the to
这与到的关系如何
the default one which which just clips
默认的只是剪辑
to a list the answer is that it's
到列表中，答案是
exactly the same the the default one is
完全相同，默认值是
exactly it's just the same as this
完全一样
except instead of having a to set
除了没有设置
collector embedded but then it it's got
嵌入了收集器，但是它有
a two list collector embedded within it
嵌入其中的两个列表收集器
so it works in just the same way it's
所以它的工作原理与
just they obviously thought it was
他们显然以为
convenient for you to have a default but
方便您默认但
you didn't have to think about where it
您不必考虑它在哪里
was
原为
go so that's how you that's how that
去，那就是你的方式
works mmm and so last of all on these
嗯嗯，所以最后这些
elastic on on this section there's a
在这部分有弹性
there's a collector which applies a
有一个收集器
function before the values are processed
在处理值之前起作用
and you might think why would I want to
你可能会想为什么我要
do that I mean that doesn't sound like a
那是不是听起来像一个
very sensible thing to do because after
非常明智的事情，因为之后
all one of the one of the most common
最常见的一种
operations intermediate operations of
操作中间操作
streams is a map operation right
流是地图操作权
so if which applies a function to each
因此，如果哪一个功能适用于每个
value so if okay the so if I could apply
值，所以如果可以的话，如果我可以申请的话
a function to each value as it's coming
每个值的功能
down the stream why would I want to
顺流而下我为什么要
collector which is going to do exactly
收集器将要做的确切
the same thing so maybe maybe maybe you
同样的事情，也许也许你
can think about why why we would want
可以思考为什么我们要
that given the the what I just talked
鉴于我刚才所说的
about with the downstream collectors
关于下游的收集者
absolutely you might need a map in a
绝对你可能需要一张地图
downstream collector because what you
下游收集器，因为你
might want to do is after the first
可能想做的是在第一次之后
collections taking place you might then
您可能会进行收集
want to do some processing on the on the
想要对进行一些处理
elements that come out before you
在你面前出现的元素
collect them again and we'll see
再次收集它们，我们将看到
examples of this is that's really quite
这样的例子是真的
a common thing you want to do so
您想这样做的共同点
supposing you want for example to you're
假设你想要例如
interested in a certain piece of
对某一片感兴趣
information from a remote from our value
远离我们价值的信息
but you also want to have the whole
但你也想拥有整个
value as well for later processing so
以及后续处理的价值
what you would do is you would do the
你会做的是你会做
classification on that on that initial
对该首字母进行分类
piece you passed through your value and
您通过价值传递的一块
then you would extract whatever else you
然后你会提取其他任何东西
need for later on so that's it so it's
以后需要的就是这样
actually pretty useful I mean if I make
实际上非常有用，我的意思是如果我做
it look like a like a if I put it in
如果我把它放进去的话
this kind of way it looks pretty stupid
这种方式看起来很愚蠢
because you could get the same effect as
因为您可以获得与
this just by putting a map operation on
这只是通过将地图操作
the stream so what but I did it this way
溪流怎么办，但我是这样做的
for the animation because the animation
对于动画，因为动画
is really complicated if if I do
如果我这样做真的很复杂
anything else and then I'll show you
还有别的，然后我告诉你
I'll show you more realistic example so
我会给你展示更现实的例子
here so here that this is a mapping
在这里，这是一个映射
operator and it has the the downstream
运算符，它具有下游
collector is to set by the look of it so
收藏家是由它的外观设置
the the mapping is person get city and
映射是人获取城市，
the downstream operator is set so what
设置下游运算符
we're going to get here is a is a set of
我们要去这里是一组
of the city
城市的
that people live in and obviously you
人们住在那里，显然你
could do the same thing there just by
可以在那里做同样的事情
just mapping person to city in the
只是将人映射到城市中
stream but but in the next example that
流，但在下一个示例中
I'll show you then you couldn't you
我告诉你，你不能
couldn't get the same thing so that's
不能得到相同的东西，那是
that's the animation example but oh
那是动画的例子，但是哦
something went wrong there I'd it that's
出现问题了，那是
alright that's that's it that's more
好吧，仅此而已
sense of that's a more sensible example
感觉是一个更明智的例子
so so here what we've got is probably
所以在这里我们可能有
not very sensible we've got where we're
不是很明智，我们在哪里
going to group people by the city and
要按城市分组
then we're going to map the the names of
然后我们要映射的名称
the people that that we're gonna sorry
我们会后悔的人
we're going to map that the person those
我们要映射那个人
person objects to the to their names and
人反对他们的名字，
then we're going to collect them in the
然后我们将它们收集在
downstream collector which will be
下游收集器
joining so what we'll get then out of
加入所以我们将从中得到什么
that is concatenation of the names of
这是名称的串联
all the people that live in each city so
住在每个城市的所有人
London will have John and Bill on
伦敦将有约翰和比尔
whatever it was and can cut it can
无论过去是什么，都可以削减
catenate it together and there's a
一起分类，有一个
significant number of these convenience
这些便利中有大量
of these of these various collectors
这些不同的收藏家中
which correspond to other to operations
与其他操作相对应
on the on both on the intermediate
在中间
operations like mapping which
像映射这样的操作
corresponds to the map intermediate
对应于地图中间
operation and a lot of and a lot of
操作和很多很多
factory collectors which correspond to
对应的工厂收藏家
terminal operations that you want that
您想要的终端操作
you want to incorporate into collectors
您想纳入收藏家
later on so for example you could vary
以后，例如，您可能会有所不同
an in-stream you can count the number of
您可以计算插播广告的数量
elements on it well for a for as a if
元素就可以了
you want to downstream collector that
您想要下游收集器
can do the same thing it's created by
可以做同样的事情
the counting factory method of the
的计数工厂方法
collectors class and same for Max and
收藏家类，与Max和
min which which will give you max by and
最小，这将为您带来最大的和
and min by and these are these these
和分钟，这些是这些
methods do exactly the same thing but
方法做完全一样的事情，但是
you can put them into you can use them
你可以把它们放入你可以使用它们
to create collectors that you can use
创建可以使用的收集器
you can use for downstream collectors so
您可以用于下游收集器
some average summary statistics summary
一些平均摘要统计摘要
statistics gives you the sum the count
统计信息给您总和计数
the minimum and maximum and the average
最小，最大和平均值
so that's so that's a kind of useful
所以这是一种有用的
object and again you can get that both
对象，你可以再次得到
ways and even and even the reductions
方式，甚至减少
can be done
可以做到
okay so so last thing I want to talk
好，所以我想谈的最后一件事
about before before the break because
大约在休息之前
we're just coming up to the hour is the
我们只是到了一个小时
concurrent collection so concurrent
并发收集，所以并发
thread safety I've said thread safety is
线程安全我说过线程安全是
guaranteed by the framework even for non
由框架保证，即使对于非
thread safe components so I mean this
线程安全组件，所以我的意思是
this is this is a big plus because quite
这是一个很大的优点，因为
a lot of the time you if you're writing
很多时候，如果你在写
your code so it's gonna be parallel
您的代码，因此它将是并行的
ready then you don't know in principle
准备好了，那么你原则上不知道
you don't know whether it's going to be
你不知道是否会
from now on you don't know whether your
从现在开始你不知道你是否
code is going to be executed
代码将要执行
sequentially or in parallel so since
顺序或并行
it's probably going to be executed
它可能会被执行
sequentially for some time to come it
连续一段时间来
doesn't make much sense to start right
正确开始没有多大意义
start writing two concurrent collections
开始编写两个并发集合
but you have a bigger over which have a
但是你有一个更大的
big overhead just because they're
很大的开销只是因为他们
thread-safe so you would want to use non
线程安全的，所以您想使用非
safe non throw safe collections you're
安全非抛出安全集合
going to carry on using hash set and
将继续使用哈希集和
hash map and all that kind of thing so
哈希图和所有类似的东西
it's a big plus that the content that
这是一大优点
the framework says I don't care whether
框架说我不在乎
you're whether when that change you have
你是什​​么时候改变的
takes place
发生
would you sequential and parallel
你会顺序和并行
execution you don't and you're not gonna
处决你不会，你不会
have to worry about it I'll look after
不用担心我会照顾的
it so I will look after thread safety
所以我会照顾线程安全
whether it's sequential or whether it's
无论是顺序的还是连续的
parallel this and this is actually
与此平行，这实际上是
really kind of a big bonus and in years
几年来确实是一大笔红利
to come as the technology for
作为技术来
parallelizing code becomes better you'll
并行化代码会变得更好
really be grateful for this because you
为此我真的很感激，因为你
because increasingly you're just going
因为越来越多的你只是去
to get this benefits of parallel
得到并行的好处
execution for free or not exactly for
免费执行或不完全执行
free but really really cheaply all you
免费，但真的很便宜
have to do is change stream to parallel
要做的就是将流更改为并行
stream and everything will still work
流，一切仍将正常
perfectly and so that's that's quite a
完美，这就是相当
big plus but in some cases you actually
大加，但在某些情况下，您实际上
know that you're the in you're going to
知道你是内在的
have to use a thread safe container
必须使用线程安全的容器
already right from the start so you to
从一开始就已经正确，所以您
so maybe you're collecting into a you're
所以也许你正在收集到一个
collecting into a concurrent map which
收集到并发映射中
is already being used by by other by
已经被其他人使用
other threads and so it needs to manage
其他线程，因此需要管理
its own thread safety so in that case
它自己的线程安全性，因此在这种情况下
you're
你是
the the the framework will still work
该框架仍将有效
fine if you use grouping by for example
如果您使用分组方式，例如
or to map it will still work fine but it
或映射它仍然可以正常工作，但是
will impose the overhead of thread-safe
会增加线程安全的开销
execution on to your on to your
执行到你的
collection and your collections already
收藏和您的收藏已经
thread-safe so now you're going to be
线程安全的，所以现在您将成为
paying for the thread safety twice over
两次为线程安全付费
which seems like a kind of poor deal and
这似乎是一笔可怜的交易，
so the so grouping by into map all have
所以按地图分组
these all have these extra overloads
这些都有这些额外的过载
that allow for that allow for
允许，允许
concurrency every overload of to map and
并发性的每个重载映射和
grouping by has a dual two concurrent
分组具有双重两个并发
map and grouping by concurrent and and
通过并发和进行映射和分组
in that way the you you don't have to
这样，您就不必
pay twice if you already know that your
如果您已经知道自己的付款，请支付两次
collection is going to be thread safe
集合将是线程安全的
then you can then you can take it then
然后你可以然后你可以拿走
you can take advantage of that okay
你可以利用那好吧
right so we've reached 930 fantastic
对，所以我们已经达到了930分
timing even considering that the
时间甚至考虑到
problems with the the cable so I'm so I
电缆有问题，所以我就这样
know it's quite a long time it's a two
知道很长一段时间是两个
hours is quite a long time to sit
坐了很长时间
through somebody and chattering at you
通过某人和你聊天
so I think a five minute comfort breaks
所以我想休息五分钟
quite a good idea before we stop though
虽然停下来之前还是个好主意
are there any questions on the first
首先有什么问题吗
half yes
一半是
right so the question is well how can
对，所以问题很好
you know where you are in the collection
你知道你在集合中的位置
supposing you suppose you've you want to
假设你想你想
do something to every third element of
对第三个元素做某事
the stream if you start thinking about
如果您开始考虑流
so there are kind of there are ways in
所以里面有些办法
which you can do this and but mostly
您可以做到这一点，但主要是
they involve actually attaching the
他们实际上涉及附加
attaching an index value to the value
将索引值附加到该值
before it starts down the stream and if
在它开始流之前，如果
you and if you think that sounds crude
你，如果你觉得这听起来很粗糙
and you can't understand why the stream
而且你不明白为什么流
API doesn't offer that think about
API不提供这种考虑
trying to do this with a with the
试图用
collection that's being executed and
正在执行的收集
it's being processed in parallel
它正在并行处理
supposing supposing I've got a million
假设我有一百万
element array and I want to chop it up
元素数组，我想把它切碎
into pieces I and I and now you tell me
碎成碎片我和我，现在你告诉我
how you want to know where in the total
您想如何知道总数
array each element occurs you want to
排列每个要发生的元素
have some way of doing that so there's a
有一些方法可以做到，所以有一个
huge overhead in in providing that you'd
提供您所需的巨大开销
have to provide the starting value
必须提供初始值
actually I'm going to do something quite
其实我会做一些相当
like that in the in the in the example
就像例子中的
in the example at the end but you'll see
在最后的示例中，但您会看到
that there's an overhead involved and
有开销，
since it's not the thing that people
因为这不是人们的事
most commonly want to do and because
最常想做的，因为
it's difficult to do with parallel
用并行很难做到
processing they don't provide it out of
处理他们不提供它
the box yes
盒子是
sorry
抱歉
well you could you could run them
好吧，你可以运行它们
through a filter that's probably that's
通过一个过滤器可能是
that's the that's the generic solution
那就是通用解决方案
that the stream a sorry the question was
那个流很抱歉的问题是
how do you validate them and the answer
您如何验证它们和答案
is a generic solution that that the
是一种通用的解决方案
stream API offers is the filter is the
流API提供的是过滤器
filter operation there really isn't
过滤操作确实没有
anything else that it would allow you to
任何其他可以让您
yeah that's it I think yeah yeah I mean
是的，我想是的，我的意思是
I think I select the answer to your
我想我选择了您的答案
question yeah
是的
so so the question is what if you want
所以问题是如果你想要
to do things would essentially want to
做事情本质上是想
do things twice for the stream elements
为流元素做两次
and that's that's quite a II basically
这基本上是一个II
that was a design aim of this of the
这是这个的设计目标
stream designers so you can't do most of
流设计师，因此您无法完成大部分工作
those things there are extensions to the
那些东西有扩展
stream libraries and I'll see if I can
流库，我看看是否可以
find some references before the end
在结束之前找到一些参考
where people have actually added new
人们实际上已经添加了新的
libraries that that I don't that onto
我没有提到的库
this that help you to do that but it's
这可以帮助您做到这一点，但这是
not part of it it's not part of the
不属于它，不属于
basic stream API okay last one and then
基本流API好，最后一个，然后
we'll break
我们会休息
this one
这个
I'm I'm using a downstream I'm using a
我正在使用下游设备，正在使用
downstream collector I'm using a
下游收集器，我正在使用
downstream collector here in exactly the
下游收集器在这里
same way as I used to list for the for
与我以前列出的方式相同
the first example this sorry Oh have I
第一个例子，对不起，我有
all right so it's so yeah there's a typo
好吧，所以是的，有错别字
yeah yeah sorry thank you for putting
是的，对不起，谢谢你的投入
out right five-minute break
出去休息五分钟
please come back or if you don't go you
请回来，或者如果你不去的话
don't want to come back just hit the
不想回来只是打
green button on my hands
我手上的绿色按钮
Jesus
耶稣
sorry I'll put them on slide no I
对不起，我把它们放在幻灯片上，不，我
know I've never done that one
知道我从来没有做过那个
he might be Stewart Marx thank you thank
他可能是斯图尔特·马克思谢谢谢谢
you well students very good too well
你很好，学生也很好
sorry I just say Stewart is very good
对不起，我只是说斯图尔特很好
and then mine too
然后也是我的
yeah yeah look out for his talks
是的，请注意他的演讲
definitely
肯定的
so you don't get the program of the
所以你不会得到
identity over the production over the
超过生产的身份
nope
不
is that better
那个更好吗
that's right the thing with a tree hello
没错，树上的东西你好
but that's working yeah yeah yeah yeah
但这是有效的是的是的是的
yeah no I think it's okay right cool
是的，不，我认为还可以，很酷
okay so yeah so you're gonna do the work
好的，是的，所以你要去做这项工作
owls oh let's let's let's have an
猫头鹰哦，让我们让我们有一个
example so first example I'm going to
例子，所以第一个例子
choose is we're going to classify people
选择是我们要对人进行分类
by age because that's right that's
按年龄，因为那是正确的
really simple people by age but after
年龄很简单的人
this it's up to you so how would we
这取决于你，所以我们怎么办
classify them by age why we're going to
按年龄分类他们为什么要
want to map from integer to person oh
想从整数映射到人哦
yes integer to person people by age
是按年龄划分的整数
people by age equals and I'll give you a
年龄相等的人，我给你
clue people dot stream that's because
线索人点流是因为
they're all going to start this way okay
他们都将以这种方式开始
Wow
哇
come on yeah yeah that's a good idea
拜托，是的，这是一个好主意
thank you I'm not very good at this
谢谢，我不是很擅长
stuff so I I often actually is it's kind
东西，所以我通常通常是这样
not it's a bit of a cop-out really to
不是，这真的有点
get you to do the work because like like
让你去做工作，因为喜欢
you'll then gonna tell me where I go
然后你会告诉我我要去哪里
wrong
错误
I hope thank you it clicked not so that
我希望谢谢你不要点击它
maybe maybe dr. dot collect grouping by
也许博士。点收集分组依据
sorry person double can't go on get it
对不起，人双不能继续得到它
age right okay see if that works
年龄合适吧，看看是否可行
Oh might be an idea to do something with
哦，可能是做某事的主意
it with the output that's out people by
它的输出结果就是
age okay so we've got a map there from
年龄还可以，所以我们在那里有一张地图
33 to a list containing Bill and Eric
33到包含Bill和Eric的列表
and 21 to Amy and 42 to John looks about
21对艾米（Amy）和42对约翰（John）
right yeah with the data at the top cool
是的，数据是最酷的
okay right so we need to choose
好吧，所以我们需要选择
something a bit harder maybe a bit
有点难一点
harder all right I'll give you one more
好吧，我再给你一个
names by age so that's gonna be a map
按年龄命名，因此将成为一张地图
well you should tell me really
好吧，你应该真的告诉我
integer 2 list of string
整数2字符串列表
name's by age stream
年龄流的名字
so if we were to downstream collected
所以如果我们去下游收集
them we've got grouping by right so it
他们我们已经正确分组，所以
was up what's going to be the
上升将是什么
classification its person like it yeah
分类喜欢它的人
age again isn't it sorry mapping okay
年龄又是不是很抱歉映射还可以
because what good because you want to do
因为有什么好想做的
some more processing
一些更多的处理
all right thank you
好哒。谢谢你们
nothing
没有
okay right sorry but it's not just a
好的，对不起，但这不只是一个
missing paranthesis it's all it's
缺少了肢体综合症
complaining about something so mapping
抱怨这样的东西映射
wants to take all right yeah no there's
想要没事吧，是的，
no default there's no default for
没有默认值，没有默认值
mapping we're gonna have to say to lists
我们要对列表说的地图
that's better so why is there no default
那更好，为什么没有默认值
well because it they didn't think there
好吧，因为他们没有想到那里
was gonna be a single common case and
将是一个普通的情况，
for that right so so we've got the names
为了这个权利，所以我们有名字
out so that that's that that's it looks
出来就是那样看起来
actually it looks remarkably like the
实际上看起来非常像
like the first one but in the first case
像第一个一样，但在第一种情况下
sorry I should have said the first one
对不起，我应该说第一个
we kind of cheated the two string method
我们有点欺骗了两个字符串方法
of person prints the name of the person
的人会打印人的名字
in inverted commas so that's what you
以逗号分隔，这就是你
were getting that's what you got the
得到的就是你得到的
first line the second line you actually
第一行第二行
got their real name
得到了他们的真名
maybe I should maybe I should maybe I
也许我应该也许我应该也许我
should have made the two string method a
应该使两个字符串方法
bit more look a bit more obvious yeah
多一点看起来更明显是的
yep so that's this is an example of why
是的，这就是为什么
you want Matt of why you want downstream
你想要马特，为什么要下游
collectors like napping that are no use
像小睡的收藏家都没有用
in their own because you because what
在他们自己，因为你因为什么
you've done is what you want here is we
您已经完成的就是您想要的是我们
want to get we want a map from from the
想得到我们想要的地图
name sorry one want a map from the age
不好意思，一个人想要一张年龄的地图
to the from one from one property of a
从一个属性的一个到一个
person to another property and you don't
一个人到另一个财产，而你不
actually work but you need to keep the
实际工作，但您需要保持
person object as a whole past the first
整个第一个人对象
past the first classification so that
过去的第一个分类，以便
you can use it later on to extract the
您可以稍后使用它来提取
second one in the right place I probably
我可能在正确的地方第二个
explain that really badly
真的很不好解释
okay let's any ideas okay I have two
好吧，让我们有任何想法好吧，我有两个
right so let's go let's have something a
对，所以我们走吧，让我们来
bit harder because this is a population
有点难，因为这是一个人口
by age that's not too hard still
按年龄，还不算太难
population by age so that's going to be
人口的年龄，这将是
a map from
来自的地图
I mean I I mean sorry okay so that's not
我是说我是对不起好吧，那不是
very clear what by population by age I
我很清楚我的年龄
mean let's click let's get a map from
意思是让我们单击让我们从中获取地图
the each age to the number of people
每个年龄段的人数
that have that age pun well you might
那个年龄的双关语很好
think that it's long yeah that's right
认为很长很对
because well we'll see I mean I mean if
因为好吧，我们将看到我的意思是
I could leave it there and then we'd get
我可以把它留在那里，然后我们得到
a really puzzling compile error but
一个非常令人困惑的编译错误，但是
because it was actually the stream the
因为它实际上是流
the compilation errors from streams and
来自流的编译错误和
not that not always that easy they're
并非总是那么容易
not that easy to construct so actually
实际上不是那么容易构建
getting the type right helps but it's
正确输入类型会有所帮助，但这是
going to be long because what we're
将会很长，因为我们
going to need to do because we we don't
需要做的，因为我们不
know how many of them that might be okay
知道其中有多少可能没问题
population by age and you'll see you'll
人口的年龄，您会看到
see that you'll see the how we get that
看到你会看到我们如何得到那个
value because people don't stream all
价值，因为人们不会流所有
right
对
grouping by now plant
按现在的工厂分组
sorry I had a mutter person age okay
抱歉，我有个喃喃自语的人，年龄还可以
and we and you want you want to just
而我们和您希望您只想
count them is that it's that all there
算是他们就在那里
is yeah this looks like that's all there
是的，这看起来就在那里
is how do I count them there's a
我怎么算他们有一个
counting collector isn't her or a clay
计数收藏家不是她还是黏土
we talked about accounting collector but
我们谈论过会计收集员，但是
actually it's a factory method called
实际上这是一种工厂方法，称为
counting which which produces which
计算哪个产生哪个
produces a collector that doesn't have a
产生一个没有
name okay population by age okay let's
按年龄命名好人口，好吧
just check that that's working okay so
只是检查它是否正常，所以
we've got 33 we've got two people
我们有33我们有两个人
twenty-one we've got one person
二十一个我们有一个人
forty-two we've got one person
四十二个，我们只有一个人
so I touched it sorry okay sorry carry
所以我感动了对不起，对不起，随身携带
on
上
certainly you could so what you could do
当然可以，所以你可以做什么
is you could provide you you could
你可以提供你可以
actually do more than just average I
实际上我做的不只是我的平均水平
mean you definitely could do that but
表示您绝对可以做到，但是
you could you could get in use in
你可以用在
summary statistics which would give you
汇总统计信息将为您提供
which will give you that and a lot of
这将为您带来很多
other information as well
其他信息
summary statistics gives you it gives
摘要统计数据给您
you and really I need a remote control
你，我真的需要一个遥控器
some statistics gives you the count the
一些统计数据可以让您
sum the average minimum and minimum and
将平均最小值与最小值相加
maximum as well but if you just wanted
以及最大，但如果您只是想
to get the let's see let's see what
让我们看看让我们看看
would happen if we just wanted to get
如果我们只想得到就会发生
the the the average does that be quite
平均的结果是相当
good wouldn't it so so well at the
很好，那不是很好吗
moment at the moment let's let's define
现在，让我们来定义
that problem average age by city okay
这个问题按城市的平均年龄还可以
average age by city average age by city
各城市的平均年龄各城市的平均年龄
right okay so that's gonna be a map from
好吧，那将是一张地图
city to double I guess average age by
我想将城市平均年龄翻一番
City
市
oh right no not necessarily I mean the
哦，对，不一定，我的意思是
the reason the reason that we had long
我们之所以很久的原因
the reason that we had long in the in
我们长期从事的原因
the last example was because counting
最后一个例子是因为计数
the counting collector that's that's
计数收集器就是
going to return long because it doesn't
将返回很长一段时间，因为它不会
know how big the I mean why should they
知道我的意思是他们为什么要大
write it for anything less than that
写不到的东西
when they when they don't know what they
当他们不知道自己在做什么
when they don't when they don't know
当他们不知道的时候
what the values are gonna have our but
价值将是我们的
if we know I mean like in this case for
如果我们知道我的意思是在这种情况下
example in oh the average age isn't
哦，平均年龄不是
going to be this there's no point in
将是这个没有意义
having a big decimal for that might be
有一个大的十进制可能是
on right so so so in this case it's it's
在右边，所以在这种情况下，是
it's we can we can just weakens we can
是我们可以，我们可以削弱我们可以
settle for a double and we could
争取双打，我们可以
probably settle for something less if we
如果我们不愿意解决的话
if we if we cared absolutely you could
如果我们绝对关心您，您可以
use it yeah I mean I mean it's a
使用它是的，我的意思是我的意思是
reference type we can have streams of
参考类型，我们可以拥有
whatever reference type rely yeah
任何引用类型都依赖
absolutely
绝对
okay so what are we gonna do and we're
好吧，我们该怎么办，我们
we're gonna click we're gonna after all
我们要点击我们毕竟
this is a talk about collectives why
这是关于集体的话题，为什么
would we do anything else routine but
我们还能做其他常规吗
whooping boy well it looks like I mean I
百岁男孩很好，看起来我的意思是我
kind of first cut at this what do you
首先切成这样你怎么办
think yeah a person get City I mean that
认为是的，一个人得到城市我的意思是
looks like that's going to work doesn't
看起来这行不通
it or something it's gonna be the start
它或它将成为一个开始的东西
rather of what we want to do so right so
而不是我们想要正确执行的操作
now what we want to do is we want to get
现在我们要做的就是我们想要得到
the total age of all the people we're
我们所有人的总年龄
gonna get the total age of all the
会得到所有的总年龄
people in the in city and then and then
在城市中的人，然后再
the count of them maybe that in summary
他们的数量也许是总结
statistics thing that might be might be
统计数据可能是
a good idea write in it sorry
一个好主意写在抱歉
well there is an average function on
嗯，有一个平均函数
that I think is an average function on
我认为这是一个平均函数
on its dream I don't know
在梦中我不知道
actually that would does a really good
其实那真的很好
question let's let's just see averaging
问题，让我们看看平均值
int it's it's averaging in the name of
诠释它的意思是平均
the collector or it's averaging in the
收集器或它的平均值
name of the yeah I think I think I think
是的，我想我想
average is the is actually the name of
平均是实际上是
the function on let me just let me just
该功能让我就让我就
cease and say since it since I says I
停下来说，因为它，因为我说我
can't remember and and it would be
不记得了，那将是
worthwhile knowing when to int stream i
值得知道什么时候int流我
okay so I don't a ver j-- so it's
好的，所以我不是veräj，所以
average right okay so we need to we need
一般吧，所以我们需要
to get the what we need to do is to get
得到我们需要做的就是得到
the the ages into a stream and then to
古往今来，然后
average that stream right that's what we
平均流的权利，这就是我们
need to do now how M do that
现在需要做M怎么做
right averaging let's try the averaging
正确的平均，让我们尝试平均
averaging int to int function so it
将int平均为int函数，因此它
sounds good doesn't it takes a takes a
听起来不错，不是需要花一个
takes of T and it's a map and it takes a
取T，这是一张地图，取一个
mapper I like that okay so what would be
映射器我喜欢这样，那会是什么
what would we expect to put in there
我们希望在那里放什么
then person person dot your age person
然后有人点你的年龄人
kind of get age yeah okay right so is
有点年纪了，好吧，也是
exactly that give us our answer it seems
正是这给了我们我们的答案，似乎
to be saying that it does this is what
可以说是这样做的
this is why I like to do this stuff
这就是为什么我喜欢做这个东西
interactively because somebody generally
交互式的，因为通常有人
knows a better answer than I do
知道比我更好的答案
this let's have a look
这让我们看一下
Londyn 33 tulsa 42 and athens 27 london
伦敦33塔尔萨42号和雅典27号伦敦
40 london 33 well okay athens 27 tulsa
40伦敦33好的雅典27塔尔萨
42 looks good
42看起来不错
sorry
抱歉
sorry I didn't catch that could you say
对不起，我没听清楚你能说什么
it again well because because we have no
因为我们没有
way of saying I mean like it's like in
我的意思是说就像
this case we're averaging that we're
在这种情况下，我们平均而言
averaging the age for each city I mean
平均每个城市的年龄
in general I mean for a real-life
一般来说，我指的是现实生活
problem you're I mean for a real-life
问题，我的意思是现实生活
problem and you're doing some data
问题，您正在做一些数据
processing you're gonna expect to have
处理您将要拥有的
more than one person per city but but
每个城市多于一个人，但
the how much work your idea is that
你的想法是多少工作
we're doing too much work because
我们做太多的工作，因为
sometimes they'll be cities with only
有时他们会是只有
one person or no people in them but if
一个人或其中没有人，但如果
there's no people in them then then
那时没有人
there won't be then there won't be any
不会再有任何事
extra work if there's if there's one
如果有的话，额外的工作
person yes there would be some there
人是的，那里会有一些
would be some work yeah but you know
是一些工作，但是你知道
it's programming so that happens cool
它正在编程，所以很酷
okay that's it that's a good problem any
好吧，那是个好问题
others are we doing for turn now we
其他人我们现在在转弯
still got a bit we still got a bit of
还有一点，我们还有一点
time another ten minutes or so
再过十分钟左右
okay let's have something I'll provide
好吧，让我来提供一些东西
one then how about this cities cities
那这个城市怎么样
with more than one with more than one
多于一多于一
inhabitant
居民
slightly different
稍微不一样
sorry
抱歉
I would need to put I'm certainly gonna
我肯定要说
need to have a filter in there
需要在那里有一个过滤器
what was my tech what's the type I'm
我的技术是什么类型
headed for here cities with more than
前往这里的城市
one inhabitant the Elissa a set of
一个居民艾丽莎（Elissa）
cities were some of a set up city
城市是一些已建立的城市
or column popular cities though they're
或纵排热门城市
not actually they don't you have to be
其实他们不是，你不必
very populist for this today more than
今天的民粹主义者比
one inhabitant okay so we're going to
一个居民好吧，我们要
need to we can't do it we can't put a
需要我们做不到的我们不能把
filter on straight away because we don't
立即过滤，因为我们不
have the information that we need now
拥有我们现在需要的信息
first of all we're gonna have to do a
首先，我们要做一个
collection aren't we we're gonna have to
收集不是我们要
we're gonna have to a collective
我们要去一个集体
grouping by so what are we going that
分组，那么我们要做什么
we're going to group by right City so
我们将按正确的城市分组，以便
then we're going to do the counting so
然后我们要进行计数
now what do we have we've got so what
现在我们有什么我们有什么
was so what we've got at this point is a
所以我们在这一点上是
map from person to the which actually
从人到实际映射
what's really quite useful list is to
真正有用的清单是
actually write out where you are at this
实际写出你现在在哪里
point so we've got a map from city too
点，所以我们也有一张城市地图
long right so for each city I've got
没错，所以对于每个城市，我都有
I've got the the city reach city I've
我有我到达的城市
got I've got the other map which maps
我有另一张地图
each city to the number of inhabitants
每个城市的居民人数
in there sorry
在那对不起
I have to you have to do I have to do
我必须要做你必须要做
another stream but what am I going to
另一个流，但我要去
stream now this is something I haven't
现在流这是我没有的东西
told you about this is something you
告诉你这是你的事
have to do quite often for these
必须经常做这些
problems I'm gonna have to break this
我要打破这个问题
map down I can't stream a map directly
向下地图我无法直接流式地图
I'm gonna have to get the empty set of
我将不得不拿空套
it you know so now that's and now what
你知道所以现在就是现在
I've got is a set of entries each one of
我有一组条目，每个条目
them associating a city with along so
他们将城市与之联系在一起
now I could do the filter thing what you
现在我可以做过滤器的事情你
want sorry okay so so I've gone so I've
想要对不起，所以我走了，所以我已经
got an entry and and and and I want to
有一个条目，并且和，而我想
check whether the value okay that is
检查值是否还可以
probably it'll probably get this right
可能会正确
when when when it'll when we've got the
什么时候什么时候什么时候我们有了
we got all written if it doesn't I can
如果不是的话，我们都写了
go back and I can I can give an explicit
回去，我可以给一个明确的
type to the what do I got wrong sorry oh
输入我该怎么办才对不起哦
yeah thank you oh look all the Reds come
是的，谢谢，哦，所有的红军都来了
away that's fantastic right so so now we
离开那太棒了，所以现在我们
now we've got a set of the entries we've
现在我们有一组条目
got we've got a stream of the entries
得到了条目流
and we've knocked out all the ones we
我们已经淘汰了所有我们
don't want so all so I think all we need
不想那么所有，所以我认为我们需要
to do now is just recover the names of
现在要做的只是恢复名称
the cities is that right okay so we want
城市是正确的，所以我们想要
to oh I shouldn't have done that
到哦，我不应该那样做
how are we gonna get those out collect I
我们怎么去把那些收集起来
mean what's gonna be the collector here
意思是这里的收藏家
alright so I do I do want I do want to
好吧，我愿意，我想要
sit but well at the moment what I've got
坐好，但目前我所拥有的
there's still the entries right I
我仍然有条目
haven't I haven't actually broken the I
我还没有真正打破过我
haven't actually broken the city out of
并没有真正使这座城市脱离
there I'm going to need to I'm going to
我需要的是
need to put a map in anti so I'm going
需要在地图上放置反图，所以我要
to need to map from to map my entry get
需要映射来映射我的条目
which of them what do I want
他们当中哪些我想要
is it it is key right okay
是关键吗好吗
and now I want to collect that to assert
现在我想收集它来断言
how about that
那个怎么样
see if that works
看看是否可行
okay so only athens has more than one
好吧，所以只有雅典有一个以上
person that this is after the apocalypse
启示录之后的人
right yeah okay so that worked right
对，是的，所以工作正常
okay we got time for one more yeah we've
好吧，我们还有时间再做一次
got time for one more yeah
有时间再来一次
if it's in map on the stream and mapping
如果它在流中的地图和地图中
as this it's a it's a factory method in
因为这是一种工厂方法
the collectors class so the difference
收藏家阶层，所以区别
between those is that map is an
在这些之间是地图是
intermediate operation which is applied
中间操作
to every value as it comes down the
跌落到每个价值
stream changes each values it comes down
流改变了它下降的每个值
the stream if you want to do that once
流，如果你想做一次
you're actually if you want to collector
你实际上是想收集的人
that is going to do that before it does
那要先做
its collection in other words if it's
换句话说，如果它是
going to take an incoming stream and
将采取传入流和
apply an operation to it you need to you
对您进行操作
need to have a different kind of
需要有一种不同的
collector so you are rather you need to
收藏家，所以你宁愿你需要
modify the collector you need to take
修改您需要的收集器
your downstream collector and you say I
你下游的收藏家，你说我
want something done before that and
想要在那之前做点什么，
mapping takes the downstream collector
映射需要下游收集器
and there's something that you want done
还有你想做的事情
before that and it puts them together to
在那之前，它们把它们放在一起
make a new collector okay one more then
再找一个新的收藏家
this they're getting a bit harder and by
他们变得越来越难了
the way there's a we've got a hands-on
的方式，我们有动手
lab tomorrow which which will stretch
明天进行实验
you really a bit further than a bit
你真的远不止于此
further than this it's quite this really
比这更远的是
quite interesting but it's a it's a
很有意思，但这是一个
hands-on lab for streams and Landers and
溪流和着陆器的动手实验室以及
it's really well it's really well graded
真的很好，而且评分真的很好
it's Stewart Stewart marks from Oracle
这是Oracle的Stewart Stewart标记
has made that made that lab cooperated
使那个实验室合作了
with him a bit but he's done the huge
和他在一起，但是他已经做了很多
amount of work on it so I strongly
大量的工作，所以我坚决
recommend that to you if it's not full
建议您，如果不满
up already right so most popular age
已经是正确的，所以最受欢迎的年龄
responses from is actually quite
来自的回应实际上是
interesting
有趣
yeah there's even more difficult to get
是的，更难得到
the I mean we probably don't have time
我的意思是我们可能没有时间
to get them that you would just want you
让他们知道你只想要你
would just want an inter an integer I
只是想要一个整数我
mean we're really kind of we're really
意味着我们真的很我们
taking a punt here on on what we're
在这里谈论我们的情况
going to get out
要出去
in fact we'll see that that isn't right
实际上，我们会发现这是不对的
either but we'll let's see why
要么，但让我们看看为什么
sorry well the murder is like if you've
对不起，谋杀就像你
got ten people that are 33 years old and
有十个人33岁
12 people that are 42 years old 42 is
42岁的12个人42是
the most popular age you want a grouping
您想要分组的最流行年龄
by
通过
right so now we've got and in the way
对，所以现在我们有了
that I in the way that I like to write
以我喜欢写的方式
it we've got a map from I've got a map
我们有一张地图，我有一张地图
from age in integer well in digital
从年龄开始以整数表示
persons so far but but obviously that's
到目前为止的人员，但显然这是
we're going to need to change that sorry
我们将需要更改对不起
it's it's it's yeah you're absolutely
是的，是的，你绝对
right it's to a list of person yeah
对的是一个人的名单
thank you
谢谢
so so we're it right so what I think
所以我们是对的，我的想法
counting sounds counting sounds good
数数声音数数声音很好
because that's going to enable us to
因为那将使我们能够
find the maximum the maximum isn't it so
找到最大值，不是最大值
so where's the counting it where's the
所以在哪里算呢
counting gonna go here we could put in
数数要去这里，我们可以把
we could put in now straight away you
我们可以马上把你放进去
don't think so so so we would then get a
别这么想，所以我们会得到一个
map from integer to integer too long and
从整数到整数的映射太长，并且
that would be and that's actually going
那将是，实际上正在
to have the information that we need in
拥有我们需要的信息
there isn't it
没有
because because yeah that's right
因为是的，没错
because it's actually going to have the
因为它实际上将具有
count it's going to have the age and
算是要有年龄了
it's going to have the count for each
每一个都有计数
one so I like that so I think if I just
一个，所以我喜欢，所以我想如果我只是
say counting now right then I think that
说现在算，那我想
then I think that we probably oh that
那我想我们可能是
was not what I meant to do
不是我的本意
so what we need to do now now we've got
所以我们现在需要做的是
now we've got a map which has got as now
现在我们有一张地图了
it's er I should change that now to from
我应该现在将其更改为
being from being list of person to being
从被列出的人到被
long and now what we've got to do is
好久了，现在我们要做的是
we've got to analyze the entries in that
我们必须分析其中的条目
map to sort of invert it really because
映射某种程度上将其反转真的是因为
well max value I think you know I think
好最大的价值，我想你知道我想
there's a there's a some kind of there's
那里有某种
a max by function on I think on on
我认为在功能上最大
streams is that right
流是正确的
maybe I know but it's got to be if we
也许我知道，但是如果我们
had a stream you've got a max by and you
有了一个流，您获得了最大的收益，而您
provide a comparator and it's going to
提供一个比较器，它将
order the elements according to the
根据
columns and then you could just get the
列，然后您可以获取
the that would give you the one you want
那会给你你想要的那个
it but we need to have a stream of these
它，但我们需要有这些
these of these entries so I need to I
这些条目的这些，所以我需要我
need to I need to put in entry set again
需要我需要再次输入条目集
all right okay dot entry set dot stream
没事吧，点输入设置点流
now that now why isn't it doesn't like
现在为什么现在不喜欢
that max list it's not called max by
最大列表，它不被称为max
it's called max max by is the name of
它称为max max by是
the function of the method that the
该方法的功能
factory method that produces home
产生家的工厂方法
a collector the desert so the comparator
一个收集者沙漠，所以比较者
we want here is now there is some clever
我们想要这里现在有一些聪明
stuff in java 8 and they gave us what we
Java 8中的东西，他们给了我们什么
could do is we could obviously we could
可以做的是，我们可以显然可以
define a lamb that we said given an
定义我们说过的羔羊
entry the the one that the one o the
进入那个一个或一个
return the result of comparing the
返回比较结果
values which is what which is what we're
价值观，这就是我们
probably interested in here isn't it
可能对这里感兴趣不是吗
yeah but
好但是
there is a method in map entry
在地图输入中有一种方法
so it's map entry dot comparing by value
因此它是地图输入点按值进行比较
fantastic that's the one we want isn't
太棒了，我们想要的不是
it
它
because we want to compare the to
因为我们要比较
compare the council's and it's gone
比较理事会的，它已经不存在了
again no no it's no no it's got to the
再次，不，不，不，不，必须
point where I can't even touch the
我什至无法触摸的地方
machine that's going to make it
可以做到的机器
difficult okay so I think that's it
很难，好吧，我想就是这样
is that right I am gonna get an optional
是的，我会得到一个可选的
in yeah I was waiting for that to come
是的，我在等那件事
up as a compiler so yeah so I need to I
作为编译器，是的，所以我需要我
need actually to get the I need to get
实际上需要得到我需要得到
the the I do need to map I do need to
我需要地图我需要
map it don't I okay so I want to so but
映射它不行，所以我想
what I've got now is what I've got now
我现在拥有的就是我现在拥有的
is an is the entry isn't it so I so I
是一个条目是不是所以我所以我
want to do a get value isn't it isn't it
想获得价值不是吗？
shouldn't we get value you know it's not
我们不应该获得价值，你知道那不是
it's not it's not offering me ah because
不是不是没有提供我啊，因为
the reason why it's not offering me yet
它还没有提供我的原因
it's not offering me that because it
它没有提供我，因为它
knows that it knows it's gonna return an
知道它知道会返回一个
optional I mean I knew it was going to
可选，我的意思是我知道它将要
return an optional I didn't want to to
返回一个我不想的可选
just spoil your fun
破坏你的乐趣
the reason it's going to return an
它要返回的原因
optional is because what I'm doing is
可选的是因为我正在做的是
I'm trying to get the largest value out
我正在努力获取最大的价值
of a stream with the max method but of
使用max方法的流
course we don't know we can't tell them
当然我们不知道我们不能告诉他们
advance that it's going to be anything
前进，它将是任何东西
in that stream right so so if so the
在那个流中，所以，如果是这样，
result of that the the consequence is
结果的结果是
then what we're going to get what we're
然后我们将得到我们所得到的
going to get back is an optional int fun
要回来是一个可选的诠释乐趣
so second
那么第二
if I have to introduce a maximum this
如果我必须介绍一个最大的
particular this code isn't gonna isn't
特别是这段代码不会
is going to just choose one of them
将只选择其中之一
absolutely there is a more complicated
绝对有一个更复杂的
version of this code which we don't have
该代码的版本，我们没有
to which we aren't gonna have time to do
我们没有时间去做
but that it is in the book which which
但这是在书中
actually allows you to to get to get
实际上让你得到
back and the full map I'll choose this
返回和完整的地图，我会选择这个
or choose a set of the most the most
或选择一组最
popular ones right so what do I need to
受欢迎的，所以我需要什么
do to this to this optional to get to
为此选择此选项以获取
pull the D so where would I wear when I
拉D，这样我在哪里穿
map there where would I map the empty to
映射在那里我将空映射到哪里
the to the key I'm gonna have to do that
我要去做的关键
after after the max I don't think so
在最大之后我不这么认为
actually I think I probably wouldn't I
其实我想我可能不会
make my life easier if I wouldn't I tell
如果我不告诉我，我的生活会更轻松
you what would make my life actually
你是什​​么让我的生活真正
easier would be would be in fact instead
实际上会更容易
of that I mean I could do that but what
我的意思是我可以做到，但是
would actually make my life easier would
实际上会让我的生活更轻松
be to map this to the get to get to get
将此映射到获取获取
the value how do I need to only don't
价值我只需要不需要
need the key right okay it's I'm
需要正确的钥匙好吧，我是
comparing by value but now I need the
按价值比较，但现在我需要
key don't I map I'm so so I'm going to
关键我不映射我是，所以我要
say map entry
说地图入口
you get key right right
您正确地获得了钥匙
okay so I want to say or else or else or
好吧，我想说，否则，否则，或者
else - one right
其他-一项权利
oops and and now that and now this is
哎呀，现在，现在，这是
not gonna be right because actually I'm
不会是对的，因为实际上我是
surprised I know right
惊讶我知道是对的
I thought I could have done worse I
我以为我会做得更糟
could also have defined this as an
也可以将其定义为
optional int which is which is what I
可选的int这就是我
was invited to right let's see if that
被邀请到右边，让我们看看
works that didn't well and possibly
作品效果不佳，可能
printing it out would be a good idea
打印出来是一个好主意
thank you
谢谢
it's a popular age let's see what
这是一个受欢迎的时代，让我们看看
happens
发生
cool I'm the most popular age is in fact
我最流行的年龄其实
30 to 33 in our data all right so we've
数据中的30到33很好，所以我们已经
got two people with 33 what do you think
有两个33岁的人，你怎么看
doable guys at the front think it's
前面的可行的人认为这是
doable you guys at the back I know it's
你们在后面做得好，我知道
a big room isn't it it takes a bit
房间很大不是吗
it takes a bit of getting your head
需要一点头
around it right but but it is but you
围绕它，但它却是你
can see that it is doable I've made it
可以看到这是可行的，我做到了
look a bit easier than then you'll find
看起来比那时容易一些
it because you will get a lot of stupid
因为你会变得很愚蠢
compilation errors they're not stupid
编译错误，它们并不愚蠢
it's just right really difficult to sort
真的很难排序
out and you have to do some you have to
出去，你必须做一些你必须做的
do some reasonably smart things to like
做一些相当聪明的事情来喜欢
I mean extract variable for example
我的意思是例如提取变量
really helps a lot
真的有很大帮助
sometimes the compilation errors are
有时编译错误是
quite misleading so you have to you have
很有误导性，所以您必须拥有
to kind of think your way through it a
思考一下自己的方式
bit but you can see that you'll get it
一点，但是你会看到你会得到它
we're getting quite a lot of quite a lot
我们得到了很多很多
of power the quite complex functions out
力量相当复杂的功能
of doing at putting together pretty
做漂亮的事情
simple things now that idea of the you
简单的事情现在你的想法
know the UNIX tool philosophy of putting
知道UNIX工具的放置原理
simple things together to make bigger
简单的事情一起做大
ones works pretty well here and it's a
在这里效果很好，这是一个
lot of a lot of how it works is the
它是如何工作的
composition of the of the different
不同的组成
collectors and to some extent as well
收藏家，在某种程度上
the composition of the the composition
组成的组成
of the intermediate operations into the
中间操作进入
streams okay I'm going to go back to the
流好吧，我要回到
slides now just do just to round things
幻灯片现在只是为了解决问题
off because they're pretty much out of
离开，因为他们几乎没有了
time
时间
oh we were sure about me
哦，我们对我有把握
time right still just I mean not mirror
正确的时间仍然只是我的意思不是镜像
so I'm just going to I'm just going to
所以我只是要去
show you very briefly some stuff about
简单地向您展示一些有关
writing your own collector and then
写自己的收藏家，然后
we're done yeah okay so question why
我们完成了，好吧，所以问为什么
would you want to write your own
你想写自己的吗
collector well the answer is often you
收藏家很好答案通常是你
don't I mean I think you've seen now
我不是说我认为你现在已经见过
there's just a huge number of plexes in
那里只有大量的神经丛
that I mean the real problem is actually
我的意思是真正的问题实际上是
understanding that fantastic variety of
了解各种各样的
things there are in the collectors class
收藏家课里有东西
rather than rather than going off and
而不是离开
writing your own you really need to get
自己写，你真的需要得到
your head around what's on offer before
你的脑袋围绕着以前提供的东西
you start reinventing the wheel but
你开始重新发明轮子，但是
sometimes you might want to for example
有时您可能想要例如
if you wanted to accumulate to a
如果你想积累到一个
container that doesn't implement
未实现的容器
collection the library doesn't offer you
图书馆没有为您提供的收藏
much support for that or in the case
对此有很多支持
that we're going to look at now
我们现在要看
supposing you wanted to share state
假设你想分享状态
between the values being collected and
在收集的值和
that's that's that's that's what we're
那就是那就是那就是我们
gonna look at now as an example that the
现在来看一个例子
that isn't offered by the library ones
图书馆没有提供的
either
要么
so the problem right the problem I can't
所以问题解决了我无法解决的问题
remember whether I don't think I
记住我是否不认为我
described it like this in the book but
在书中这样描述它，但是
never mind anyway this is Oprah's
没关系，这是奥普拉的
problem openers problem is that these
问题开放者的问题是，这些
are the ten books that she chose the
是她选择的十本书
best ten books of the last decade and
过去十年最好的十本书
now her problem is that she that I chose
现在她的问题是我选择的她
this illustration because I was looking
这个图，因为我在看
for a set of books and I thought oh
买一套书，我想哦
right she might have some problems here
好的，她可能在这里遇到一些问题
finding a book out of her collection so
从她的收藏中找到一本书，所以
I think we should we should give her a
我想我们应该给她一个
hand with this and and the idea is of
与此手和的想法是
how we're going to solve Oprah's problem
我们将如何解决奥普拉的问题
is we're going to provide her a map from
是我们要给她提供一张地图吗
the from the name of the book from the
书名从
book to its starting point on the shelf
预定到书架上的起点
right so so and we'll do that by
是的，所以我们将通过
calculating the cumulative thickness of
计算累积厚度
all the of all the books that precede it
所有在它之前的书
because that's you know the starting
因为那是你知道的开始
point of the shelf it's obviously
架子上的点很明显
Eckhart Tolle a new earth and that's
Eckhart Tolle的新世界
that's that's at the left hand end of
那就是在左手边
the shelf and then 336 pages further on
架子上，然后继续336页
she's going to find the Poisonwood Bible
她要去寻找毒木圣经
now 336 pages of course she's not going
现在336页，她当然不会
to know the measurement of that but
知道那个的度量但是
we'll give her a conversion well
我们会给她一个很好的转换
we'll convert that into inches or
我们将其转换为英寸或
millimeters or something so that she can
毫米之类的东西，以便她可以
then fight so that she can find it and
然后战斗，以便她可以找到它，
so in this way she'll have a have a
这样她就会有一个
really easy way of finding all the books
查找所有书籍的简单方法
on her shelf of last best ten in the
在她最后十佳的架子上
last ten years you don't think there's
最近十年，你不认为有
anything strange about this at all do
对此有什么奇怪的事情吗
you
您
I got a specific request remote probe
我有一个特定的请求远程探针
for this with this code so what she
为此用这段代码，所以她
needs is a is a map from from the from
需要的是一张来自的地图
the book to its cumulative to the
这本书以其累积到
cumulative page count that precedes it
之前的累积页数
on the shelf so since new earth is at
在架子上，所以既然新地球在
the far left-hand side that the
在最左侧
cumulative page count before that is
在此之前的累积页数是
zero but it's got 336 pages in it and so
零，但其中有336页，因此
the cumulative page count before the
之前的累积页数
Poisonwood Bible is 336 so that the
毒木圣经是336，因此
we're going to what we're going to do is
我们要去做的是
we're going to construct all the way I
我们将一路构建
thought about this when I was when I was
我当时想过
building this up in there for the book
在那里建立这本书
was that we're looking for a data
是我们在寻找数据
structure that's going to hold this
可以容纳这个的结构
information there's a kind of really
信息确实有一种
obvious way of doing this of course
当然，这样做的明显方式
using an accumulator but we know that
使用蓄能器，但我们知道
the accumulators are out you can't use
蓄电池没电了
accumulators with the with the stream
流的累加器
API we've got to find a way of doing it
API，我们必须找到一种方法
that it's going to that's going to be
那将会是
parallel ready so so so the idea is to
并行准备好了，所以想法是
find a data structure which which we can
找到一个我们可以的数据结构
see as provides a partial solution to
视作提供了部分解决方案
the problem and then we see how we can
问题，然后我们看如何
join together smaller bits of this data
将这些数据的较小部分合并在一起
structure to make larger ones until
制作更大的结构，直到
eventually we have the whole thing
最终我们拥有了整个东西
that's gonna be that's going to be the
那将是那将是
idea here's the here's the data
想法这里是这里的数据
structure that we're looking at the the
我们正在研究的结构
big square brackets surround a
大方括号将一个
sequential data structure which I made
我制作的顺序数据结构
in which I used for which I used an
我曾经用过
array deck in the book but actually I
书中的数组卡片组，但实际上我
think an ArrayList would be fine and
认为ArrayList会很好并且
there's be a slight performance
有轻微的表现
improvement with an array and the idea
数组和想法的改进
is that we you know we know we're going
是我们你知道我们知道我们要去
to need the accumulator the combiner for
需要累加器的组合器
the and for the for the collector and we
对于收藏家，我们
of course gonna need a supplier the
当然需要供应商
supplier is obvious it's a new ArrayList
供应商很明显这是一个新的ArrayList
or a new array deck whenever we're going
或每当我们要去一个新的阵列甲板
to use but the the accumulator is pretty
使用，但累加器很漂亮
straightforward - it takes a book a new
简单明了-需要一本新书
earth and then what it does is it
地球，然后它是做什么的
it puts the title in there it puts the
它把标题放在那里
it puts in the the number of pages and
它放入页数和
it puts in the cumulative displacement
它把累积位移
but it doesn't know that yet because
但这还不知道，因为
that's what we're trying to find out so
这就是我们试图找出的
that's going to be a zero to start off
开始将是零
with and then the then the way that the
与然后然后的方式
accumulator will work is that a single
累加器将工作的是单
thread accumulating the the first few of
线程累积前几个
these books will take a new earth first
这些书将首先崭新的地球
of all it'll make a data structure to
所有这将使数据结构
contain it and then it'll put it in in
包含它，然后将其放入
this array deck ArrayList and then it's
这个数组甲板ArrayList然后
going to then the accumulator will take
去到那累加器将采取
another one The Poisonwood Bible and it
另一本《毒木圣经》
will wrap that in the data structure and
将其包装在数据结构中，
it will and and and now it can actually
它将会并且现在它实际上可以
say what the cumulative page count is
说出累积页数是多少
and the right-hand cell where it can say
还有可以说的右侧格
what that is because it because it's
那是因为那是因为
obviously just the the cumulative page
显然只是累积页面
count from the previous one plus they
从前一个计数再加上
plus the page count from the previous
加上前一页的页数
one so it adds those two together and
一个，所以将这两个加在一起
that's how the accumulator works and now
这就是蓄能器的工作原理，现在
if we want to think how we're going to
如果我们想想我们将如何
get the whole the whole the whole thing
得到整个事情
and so imagine this is this is a
所以想象这是一个
stand-in for the for the sequential data
代表顺序数据
structure which contains all of the
包含所有
books you can see that this this can be
书中你可以看到，这可以是
made up from two partial ones suppose we
由两个部分组成，假设我们
would have two partial data structures
将具有两个部分数据结构
like this that have been constructed in
像这样的建筑
the way that I showed you on the
我向您展示的方式
previous slide the one on the left is
上一张幻灯片的左侧是
the was was built using an accumulator
它是使用蓄能器建造的
and one on the right was built using the
右边的一个是使用
accumulation now we've got to combine
现在我们必须结合起来
them together and the combination is
他们在一起，组合是
pretty straightforward what we do is we
很简单，我们要做的是
do the the combiners just takes the
组合器只需要
cumulative page count of the rightmost
最右边的累积页数
element of the left-hand half plus the
左半部分的元素加上
page count of the rightmost element of
最右边元素的页数
the left-hand half so you can see that
左半部分，这样您就可以看到
those two red arrows and that makes 976
那两个红色箭头，使976
that's the cumulative page count of the
那是
whole of the left-hand side and then it
整个左侧，然后
just adds that to every element of the
只是将其添加到
to every page count of the of the
到的每个页数
right-hand side in turn so combining
右侧依次如此结合
these two data structures doesn't
这两个数据结构不
doesn't involve you and having to have
不需要您参与，而不必
an accumulator at all we've had no
我们根本没有蓄能器
accumulator in building up this
积累这一点
cumulative page count which is which is
累积页数是
what we wanted and so that now what we
我们想要什么，所以现在我们
would do is we would take this and we
我们会做的就是
would we would run it through a stream
我们会通过流运行它吗
and we would we would project we would
我们会预测
use a map function a map operation
使用Map函数进行地图操作
to project out the the name of the book
投影出书名
and the and the and the page of the
和和的页面
cumulative page count and then we would
累积页数，然后我们将
make a map out of that so that's kind of
用它制作一张地图，这样的
that's the principle of it the full
这就是全部的原则
codes in the book I wanted to I wanted
我想要的书中的代码
to I mean I think this is it's it's a
我的意思是我认为这是
useful example because it shows how
有用的例子，因为它展示了
something which just looks like it's got
看起来像的东西
to be an accumulator actually turns out
成为一个积累者
not to have to be an accumulator we have
不必成为我们的累加器
just got our minds so welded into the
只是让我们的思想如此融合
iteration and accumulators that we don't
我们不做的迭代和累加器
see other ways of doing things even if
看到其他的做事方式，即使
they're actually pretty pretty
他们实际上很漂亮
straightforward so just to finish off I
直截了当，所以只是为了结束我
mean I did actually think about how you
意思是我确实在想你
could do this using reduction but I
可以使用减少来做到这一点，但我
guess I could skip over this pretty
猜猜我可以跳过这个漂亮的
easily the the the way that you could
轻松地以您可以的方式
get the same thing using reductions to
使用减少得到相同的东西
take each one of the the the idea that I
把每个人的想法，我
talked about earlier on if you were used
关于您是否曾经使用过
to reduction there's a functional
减少功能
programming you so hey I don't need this
给你编程，所以嘿，我不需要这个
collectors stuff I'm just gonna do it
收藏家的东西，我要做
there I'm gonna do it the tried and
在那里，我要去尝试
tested way you'd have to take each one
经过测试的方式，您必须采取每个
of these you'd have to take each one of
在这些中，您必须将每个
these elements you'd have to make a new
这些元素，你需要做一个新的
you have to make a new data structure
您必须创建一个新的数据结构
out of it you'd have to put that in a
从它，你必须把它放在一个
sequential you have to put that in the
顺序，您必须将其放入
sequential thing just like when you're
顺序的事情就像当你
starting in the accumulator off and then
从蓄电池开始，然后
you're going to have to run reduction
你将不得不减少
over all over over all of those it's
遍及所有这些
going to be really expensive and clumsy
真的很昂贵而且笨拙
and quite a lot of it will have to be
而且其中很大一部分将是
done in client code so it's really it's
在客户端代码中完成，实际上是这样
it's really not great the Collector's
收藏家的确不是很好
was an innovation it's actually
是一项创新，实际上
something different from from what's
有别于什么
been done before it's the first time I
在我第一次做之前
think that reductions been used in a
认为减少量用于
really big way in a language that
在某种语言中确实非常重要
depends on mutation java is not a
取决于突变java不是
functional language functional languages
功能语言功能语言
by and large using immutable data
基本上使用不可变数据
structures and java is not a functional
结构和java不是功能
language and it's not going to be one so
语言，而且不会是一种语言
so adapting this side the idea of a
因此，调整这边的想法
reduction this functional idea adapting
减少这种功能性想法的适应
that into immutable containers was
变成不可变的容器是
actually really quiet it was quite a big
实际上真的很安静
breakthrough I think so it's it's pretty
突破，我认为这很漂亮
clever stuff okay so that's that's the
聪明的东西好吧，那就是
that's the sales pitch they know it's
他们知道这就是推销
now just for something else my machine
现在只是为了我的机器
is on so I'm going to talk I just talk
正在进行，所以我要说说，我只是说说
very briefly as a wrap-up while I'm
非常简短地总结一下
waiting for it to wake up about you know
等待它唤醒你知道
not responding cool I mean I'll just
没有回应很酷，我是说
talk very briefly about performance so
非常简短地谈论性能，因此
the performance of collectors is
收藏家的表现是
generally depends a lot on on the
通常很大程度上取决于
accumulator the accumulator is going to
蓄能器要去
be if you if you imagine us to kind of
如果你想像我们的话
10,000 element array then then then the
10,000个元素数组，然后
accumulator is going to be used an awful
蓄能器将被可怕地使用
lot more than the combined that the
比合并的要多得多
combined that will be used relatively
将相对使用的组合
relatively little and so just I'm just
相对较少，所以我只是
finding up and just finding my place
找到并找到我的地方
again so so the the the performs of the
再次如此，所以表演
accumulator is pretty critical and that
蓄能器非常关键，
actually really is going to be is going
实际上真的将会是
to depend on the performance of the
取决于
accumulator for the particular
特定的蓄能器
collection so generally speaking will be
所以一般来说收集是
using add the add method of different
使用添加不同的添加方法
collections for it so so that's we're
收集它，所以这就是我们
not really looking at anything very
不是很看任何东西
different from from what we have with
与我们所拥有的不同
with iterative code we're looking at
与迭代代码，我们正在看
improvements because a lot of the time
改进，因为很多时候
the the compiler can do better with with
编译器可以更好地与
stream code because a the the the it
流代码，因为它是
uses a technique which is something like
使用类似的技术
loop jamming in in in more ordinary in
循环卡入进来
conventional conventional code
常规常规代码
commercial iterative code what it does
商业迭代代码的作用
is it you can actually see and it
是您实际上可以看到的吗？
combines loops together and it gets
结合在一起的循环，它得到
better it gets better optimizations out
更好地获得更好的优化
of that the problem the biggest problem
这个问题最大的问题
I found in looking at performance of
我发现在观察
large of collectors on large data
大数据收集者
structures I mean the the kind of
结构我是指那种
simplest thing is that simplest thing to
最简单的事情是
say is that map maps are more difficult
说地图比较难
and particularly because they need to be
特别是因为他们需要
resized so resizing Maps is expensive
调整大小，因此调整地图的尺寸​​非常昂贵
and map merging which has to be done for
和地图合并，必须完成
the combat for the combiner is a very
合成器的战斗非常
expensive operation so resizing so
操作昂贵，所以调整大小
initially sizing your maps if you've got
如果您有，请先调整地图大小
if you're going to be putting a lot of
如果你要投入很多
data into a map getting the initial
数据进入地图获取初始
sized ride is actually worth a lot
大小的游乐设施实际上很有价值
so that that's a that's again a useful
所以那又是一个有用的
tip okay conclusion collectors
提示好的结论收集者
generalization of reduction they
归纳式
actually are like reduction only better
其实就像减少只有更好
they allow a functional style while
他们允许一种函数式风格
you're continuing to work in a language
你正在继续用一种语言工作
which actually it's not going to be a
实际上这不会是一个
functional language the they're really
他们真正的功能性语言
well designed to be composed together so
精心设计，可以组合在一起
you can actually do pretty fancy things
你实际上可以做一些漂亮的事情
by simply by just changing them together
只需将它们一起改变即可
I really kind of fell in love with them
我真的很爱上他们
as you can see when I was you know when
如你所见，我知道你什么时候
I really understood them properly and I
我真的很了解他们，我
think and I think I think they're really
想，我想他们真的
great they take a bit of getting used to
很棒，他们需要一点时间来适应
but then anything it's worthwhile does
但是那值得做的一切
okay so that's that's my pitch for today
好，那就是我今天的发言
I hope you enjoyed it thank you
我希望你喜欢它，谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]